<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EI on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/ei/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EI on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 14:03:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/ei/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A word of thanks</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 14:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</guid>
      <description>Founders of start-ups tend to spend a lot of time griping about things. I could write an essay on how it took from Aug 28th to Dec 3rd for Enterprise Ireland to issue a document needed to get us BES approval. Instead I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the positive part of that story.
On Dec 3rd, EI shuffled the paperwork-exercise out the door and it arrived in the Revenue Commissioners. Our solicitors also submitted our RICT outline application around the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BES/SCS Session in Rubicon</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-session-in-rubicon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 10:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-session-in-rubicon/</guid>
      <description>A workshop on the 2007-2013 Business Expansion Scheme (BES) and Seed Capital Scheme (SCS) will take place on Monday 12th November at 13:00 p.m. in the Rubicon Centre.
The Revenue Commissioners (Cillian Byrne &amp;amp; Susan Cummins) will be presenting and Gerry O’Brien, Enterprise Ireland will also be in attendance. Focused on startup and developing companies, the format is a workshop as it is intended to be interactive and give you plenty of opportunity for questions and answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is EI refusing to do any pre-work for BES?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2007 10:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</guid>
      <description>As anyone who has kicked off a BES scheme knows there are a few simple steps you have to do in order to qualify. The key one is a &amp;ldquo;New Company Cert&amp;rdquo; from Enterprise Ireland or a CEB. To qualify for the cert they generally give you a small employment grant (a Feasibility Study Grant is not sufficient). You can then go to the Revenue and start the actual BES process itself and get in-principal approval for your scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from BarCampIreland SouthEast starting to appear</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</guid>
      <description>Keith has uploaded videos of the &amp;ldquo;Finding money for your start-up&amp;rdquo; session. I enjoyed the differing views of the panel on this topic but anyone who thought they&amp;rsquo;d come away with &amp;ldquo;so that&amp;rsquo;s how I do it&amp;rdquo; would have been disappointed. There should definitely be a follow-up session at BarCamp Dublin with a focus on successful early-stage tech startup fund-raising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must-read post over at the itnorthwest Blog</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 19:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</guid>
      <description>Julian Ellison from Tablane has written the best summary of startup funding, finance and the Irish economy that I have ever read. I have one small contribution to make on it. He mentions the Business Angels Partnership and wonders how they &amp;ldquo;market&amp;rdquo; ideas that they receive.
I highly recommend that anyone with a strong well-thought out business plan just contact them and talk to them face to face. The basic way they work is that they help people who come in with strong ideas to ensure that the idea has legs and that some basic financial analysis and planning has been done.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
