<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>readwriteweb on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/readwriteweb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in readwriteweb on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 10:26:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/readwriteweb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Le Web Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/13/le-web-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 10:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/13/le-web-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I attended Le Web on Tue/Wed this week in Paris. It is the leading web conference in Europe and this was my third year.
Despite a bunch of logistical problems, Loic and Geraldine Le Meur created yet another event that will stick in the mind for a long time. I was at the conference with multiple hats on:
  CEO of LouderVoice eager to meet potential partners and investors Guest Author for ReadWriteWeb looking at Le Web from technology perspective Co-Editor of Web2Ireland looking at Le Web from business perspective   My Web2Ireland post covers the general business mood and how it may affect Irish start-ups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice covered on Read/WriteWeb</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/30/loudervoice-covered-on-readwriteweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 08:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/30/loudervoice-covered-on-readwriteweb/</guid>
      <description>We were chuffed to bits and tickled pink this morning to see that David Lenehan has done an article about Irish webapps on the very highly regarded Read/WriteWeb site and we got a mention!
Thanks guys.
He also profiled some of the older guys like Pigsback and newer ones like Pixenate, Putplace and Nooked and not forgetting PollDaddy itself.
If you liked what David had to say, maybe consider voting for it over at Digg?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
