<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Suppliers on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/suppliers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Suppliers on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 10:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/suppliers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone - Staring into the Abyss</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/12/23/vodafone-staring-into-the-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 10:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/12/23/vodafone-staring-into-the-abyss/</guid>
      <description>I have come to the conclusion that Vodafone will be roadkill on the path to ubiquitous connectivity. I&amp;rsquo;ve talked to several mobile operators in the past year and they all accept that they must become internet companies, they just don&amp;rsquo;t know how. This indecision will be fatal if Google decides to go global with Android and their spectrum purchases. Given my experiences as a simple punter in the past two weeks, can I beseech Google to buy the Three network off Hutchison Whampoa and show this relic of the 20th century what execution is all about?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Person required to do some short-term CSS&#43;XHTML work</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/20/person-required-to-do-some-short-term-cssxhtml-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 12:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/20/person-required-to-do-some-short-term-cssxhtml-work/</guid>
      <description>As LouderVoice races towards full launch, we have a requirement for someone to do CSS and XHTML work for us between now and then. Basically this person will have to take our existing design, apply it to any new features and pages on the site and tweak what is there already.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t a huge amount of work (time-scale is over the next few weeks and effort is probably less than a person-week), does not require design expertise and would suit anyone between major contracts or looking for a nice side project to exercise their mark-up muscles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggestion for FON</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/suggestion-for-fon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/suggestion-for-fon/</guid>
      <description>Given the lack of free wireless at FoWA and the disastrous wireless at LeWeb3, it struck me yesterday that conferences are the ideal opportunity for FON to give people real hands-on experience of their routers.
Imagine if the guys had provided all the wifi for free yesterday? They could still use the logon screens so they get the branding opportunities but it would have been such a coup! Maybe an idea for some of the upcoming European conferences?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Nokia</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/13/bloody-nokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 14:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/13/bloody-nokia/</guid>
      <description>I paid a fair chunk of cash for an N70 last year in the expectation that it would be the solution to all my mobile app needs for the foreseeable future and replace things like the Tungsten T. Overall it&amp;rsquo;s a fine but slow phone and there are some nice applications for it (Opera mini being particularly good). But one thing that is annoying the hell out of me is that every new announcement from Nokia seems to only be about Series 60 version 3 phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decent podcast player for Nokia N70?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/25/decent-podcast-player-for-nokia-n70/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2007 12:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/25/decent-podcast-player-for-nokia-n70/</guid>
      <description>Can anyone recommend a decent podcast player for my phone? The built-in music player is a bad joke and only suitable for playing 3 minute songs - it has no ability to jump directly to a position in an MP3. It&amp;rsquo;s use of Spanish in the status messages is also interesting.
Ideally I want something that has decent navigation capabilities within a podcast. If I could bookmark my positions in individual MP3s so I could quickly return to where I was listening, that would be awesome too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FON - Sometimes it&#39;s nice to be wrong</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/22/fon-sometimes-its-nice-to-be-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 13:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/22/fon-sometimes-its-nice-to-be-wrong/</guid>
      <description>I have written both positively and quite negatively about FON on this blog. I had no success recently with redeeming a voucher for a free router and started to wonder if it fact the reality matched the PR.
I did finally manage to order the free router by signing up with a dummy account using the same postal address as my real account. It just arrived, five weeks later. So I take it all back, those FON guys are straight up and I remain a big fan of the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java SE 6 (1.6) not compatible with Revenue Online (ROS)</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/16/java-se-6-16-not-compatible-with-revenue-online-ros/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/16/java-se-6-16-not-compatible-with-revenue-online-ros/</guid>
      <description>John Collins recently blogged that ROS no longer supported Firefox and he was unable to get support from ROS on this. I ran into the same problem last week and just used Internet Explorer instead. However last night I tried to logon and got the same problem as Firefox i.e. no error, just sent back to login screen over and over.
There are no commonalities between IE7 and FF apart from one - Sun&amp;rsquo;s JRE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Kevin McGarry of the Revenue Commissioners</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/11/28/dear-kevin-mcgarry-of-the-revenue-commissioners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 11:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/11/28/dear-kevin-mcgarry-of-the-revenue-commissioners/</guid>
      <description>If yours is the name at the end of correspondence to us, then yours is the name we ask for when we call to enquire about your letter. Those lovely harridans you have on switchboard in Dublin should then not say &amp;ldquo;oh no, he&amp;rsquo;s a director&amp;rdquo; and proceed to bounce us from one jobsworth to another. If you send letters from Dublin then expect us to ring Dublin. If that turns out to be wrong, then transfer us to Cork - I believe PBXes have had that feature for many years now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended Vendors list</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/11/28/recommended-vendors-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 09:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/11/28/recommended-vendors-list/</guid>
      <description>I did a post on this over at the LouderVoice Blog. Interested in feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I cannot run a business at 5 kb/s</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/11/28/i-cannot-run-a-business-at-5-kbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 09:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/11/28/i-cannot-run-a-business-at-5-kbs/</guid>
      <description>Recommendations please for reliable broadband in the Bandon, Cork area that makes no use of the Eircom network.
We were dead in the water for a week the last time. We&amp;rsquo;ve been crawling for 24 hours this time. BT needs to do something now about LLU or the Wimax boys will eat their dinner when it is rolled out.
Technorati Tags: Boradband, ireland, BT, Eircom, Cowboys, Amateurs, Third+World+Service, Shameless</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
