<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mobile on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mobile on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our 2009 Predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</guid>
      <description>The 2008 predictions weren&amp;rsquo;t the most accurate. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how we do for 2009.
 The Android platform will be absolutely huge. With Motorola, Sony Ericsson and a raft of Tier 2 manufacturers signed up, it will become _the _mobile platform from the mid to high end. Ignore the HTC G1, that&amp;rsquo;s just a rough first attempt by one manufacturer.  Despite Android, iPhone will remain big. There is always that 10% of the market who like paying extra for &amp;ldquo;luxury&amp;rdquo; brands SaaS ecommerce providers will go mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone - Staring into the Abyss</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/12/23/vodafone-staring-into-the-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 10:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/12/23/vodafone-staring-into-the-abyss/</guid>
      <description>I have come to the conclusion that Vodafone will be roadkill on the path to ubiquitous connectivity. I&amp;rsquo;ve talked to several mobile operators in the past year and they all accept that they must become internet companies, they just don&amp;rsquo;t know how. This indecision will be fatal if Google decides to go global with Android and their spectrum purchases. Given my experiences as a simple punter in the past two weeks, can I beseech Google to buy the Three network off Hutchison Whampoa and show this relic of the 20th century what execution is all about?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blognation Ireland Launches</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/13/blognation-ireland-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/13/blognation-ireland-launches/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m still buzzing over the fact that the blognation Ireland site has gone live. We&amp;rsquo;ve already made it to the front page of Techmeme!
As I said in the opening post:
The Irish site is part of the blognation network which is building up to be the biggest tech news site on non-US Web 2.0 startups around the globe including EMEA, Asia-Pacific, Latin America and Canada
Feel free to send me any news about your web or mobile application, no matter how early stage you are.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
