<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ryan-Carson on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/ryan-carson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ryan-Carson on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:31:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/ryan-carson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>European Start-up culture Panel at FoWA</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Carson - Carson Systems, Richard Moross - Moo, Mike Arrington - TechCrunch, Mike Butcher - Vecosys, Chris Messina - Citizen Agency, Saul Klein - Index Ventures, Max Jennings - eMomentum, Colin Donald - Futurescape, Tariq Krim - NetVibes. * Richard - Afraid of failure in Europe * Mike A - Stop talking and start doing, if we want to be like Silicon Valley. Smart people move to Silicon Valley which is a big help * Mike B - Subject is 18 months out of date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoWA Day 2</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Adobe pitch about Flex etc. Not my cup of tea.
Chris Wilson from the IE7 team. Excellent honest presentation on why they lost their way with IE. Mentioned microformats so my ears pricked up. RSS in IE7 - he&amp;rsquo;s very excited by this. I really think it&amp;rsquo;ll push the uptake of using RSS. Chris just went through all the changes in IE7 and is now going through some of the newer MS Web tools including the free ones and the VPC image with IE6 in it so you can test both IE7 and IE6 on the same machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoWA Day 1 - Seriously Good</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-1-seriously-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-1-seriously-good/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s often said about conferences that you don&amp;rsquo;t go for the speakers, you go for the networking. However, yesterday at FoWA had some of the finest presentations I have seen in the past twelve months. I ended the day buzzing with ideas for LouderVoice. Sure there was some misfires but overall Ryan had a very successful day on his hands.
Highlights for me were: * Mike Arrington - Just good solid stuff and well able to handle all the questions thrown at him (except for the Adobe Apollo ones) * Ben Holmes from Index Ventures - Loved this presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carson Workshops &#34;A-Z: How to Build a Web App&#34;</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/24/carson-workshops-a-z-how-to-build-a-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 09:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/24/carson-workshops-a-z-how-to-build-a-web-app/</guid>
      <description>0.3
A one day guide to building a Web Application Jul 24, 2006 by
Conor O&#39;Neill  event
Carson Workshops &amp;ldquo;A-Z: How to build a Web App&amp;rdquo;
 ★★★★★ Last Wednesday I attended the one day [Carson Workshop](http://www.carsonworkshops.com/) on how to build a WebApp presented by Ryan Carson. The event was held in the Energy Clinic in London and had about 15 attendees.  Ryan kicked off with a quick round-room introduction and we realised we had a very nice mix of people from funded startups, to guys looking to leave their jobs to give it a go, to companies looking to move into this area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendations for Web Application Development shops?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2006 11:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</guid>
      <description>We intend to outsource the bulk of the development of our application. This will be broken down into several areas including:
 Design XHTML/CSS Application development Hosting Operations  I have received plenty of recommendations for Design and some for XHTML/CSS but other than Ryan Carson recommending Nick in Plum Digital Media (and more on yesterday&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;How to build a WebApp&amp;rdquo; workshop later), it is proving difficult to get recommendations for top-class web application development houses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
