<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 18:45:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multiple LouderVoice Updates</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/06/24/multiple-loudervoice-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 18:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/06/24/multiple-loudervoice-updates/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy few weeks.
 Two years after LouderVoice launched with the aim to make reviews more useful via Microformats, Google announced support, followed quickly by several of our competitors. What took ye so long? Then we launched Ireland&amp;rsquo;s first Google Android Mobile application Then we enabled the use of simple #review to identify mini-reviews on Twitter Then Krishna De of Biz Growth Newsreleased an extended interview with CEO Conor all about ratings and reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest LouderVoice deployments</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/04/28/latest-loudervoice-deployments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 19:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/04/28/latest-loudervoice-deployments/</guid>
      <description>We went live on Puddleducks.ie a few weeks back and the response has been fantastic.
Today we went live with Bubble Brothers wine in Cork. They are the first users of our new SME customer reviews solution. This is a widget which can be dropped on a product page with one line of code and review-enables the entire site. No development is needed by the client and our simple job is to add the correct styling elements so that the widget blends with your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our latest customer is Puddleducks</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/04/15/our-latest-customer-is-puddleducks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 23:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/04/15/our-latest-customer-is-puddleducks/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just announced that Puddleducks.ie is the latest customer of LouderVoice for Business.
We&amp;rsquo;ll be making a lot more announcements like this in the coming weeks. Our small business solution is going live on multiple sites shortly. Contact us on business AT loudervoice DOT com if you&amp;rsquo;d like to arrange a trial. It can literally be implemented in minutes on many sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mashable Open Web Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/13/the-mashable-open-web-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 23:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/13/the-mashable-open-web-awards/</guid>
      <description>If you like what we are doing over on LouderVoice, why not vote for us in the Mashable Open Web Awards. You can do it below.
 Mashable Open Web Awards
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to vote for all your favourite Irish WebApps, many of which can be found over at Web2Ireland.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon Solutions &amp; LouderVoice BES 2008</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 11:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</guid>
      <description>We have just kicked off our BES 2008 offering which is built around the LouderVoice business. If you are interested in hearing more about this investment opportunity or discussing direct equity investments, please contact Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill on conor AT loudervoice DOT com or +353-87-9790297.
Over the past few months we have been trialling our business services with several clients. Some of those are already live, others will go live over the next quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touristr Beta Seriously Impressive</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/18/touristr-beta-seriously-impressive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 10:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/18/touristr-beta-seriously-impressive/</guid>
      <description>Jan Blanchard has been building a great travel site called Touristr for quite a while. I did some beta testing for him a while back and the potential was obvious. With their latest open beta, they&amp;rsquo;ve really improved the look and navigation of the site.
In their own words:
I think they have a winner on their hands.
Check it out here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
