<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Saul-Klein on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/saul-klein/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Saul-Klein on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:59:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/saul-klein/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SeedCamp Launches - apply now!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</guid>
      <description>At the Essential Web conference last week Saul Klein announced SeedCamp. This is an incredibly important initiative that will help grow the spirit of entrepreneurship across Europe. It basically takes a YCombinator type model and implements it here.
For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, YCombinator is hugely successful project of Paul Graham in the US. Twice a year, once in Boston, once in SV, they ask (pre)startups to apply for a slot on the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interest in a Cork OpenCoffee Club meetup next week?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 22:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Starting with Saul in London followed quickly by Eoghan in Dublin and James/Jan in Limerick, it looks like the OpenCoffee Club idea really does have legs. The core idea is that a regular informal meeting is held in a coffee shop where we try to bring together entrepreneurs and investors to discuss topics of mutual interest, learn from each other and hopefully build lasting business relationships over time.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to propose an inaugural one in Cork City for next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Start-up culture Panel at FoWA</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Carson - Carson Systems, Richard Moross - Moo, Mike Arrington - TechCrunch, Mike Butcher - Vecosys, Chris Messina - Citizen Agency, Saul Klein - Index Ventures, Max Jennings - eMomentum, Colin Donald - Futurescape, Tariq Krim - NetVibes. * Richard - Afraid of failure in Europe * Mike A - Stop talking and start doing, if we want to be like Silicon Valley. Smart people move to Silicon Valley which is a big help * Mike B - Subject is 18 months out of date.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
