<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enterprise on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/enterprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enterprise on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 17:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee off to a flying start</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 17:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</guid>
      <description>Wow that was some morning in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s! I&amp;rsquo;d never been there before and the venue was just perfect. I arrived in to find a few of the guys along with Don the owner who stayed for the entire session. A huge thanks to Don for covering the cost of the refreshments today and for getting Wifi installed with almost no notice.
We had 20+ people turn up with the exact mix I was hoping for:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first major Storage Industry Blog?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/01/24/the-first-major-strorage-industry-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2006 21:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/01/24/the-first-major-strorage-industry-blog/</guid>
      <description>We recently discovered that Hu Yoshida, Vice President and CTO of Hitachi Data Systems (HDS) has a blog. This may not seem to be a big deal to many people but it is actually a very major change on several different levels by one of the top players in a traditionally secretive industry.
The storage industry has been built entirely on a foundation of proprietary technologies until quite recently. There are very few companies operating in this space at the top end; HP, EMC, IBM and HDS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The future of Enterprise Software</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/01/05/the-future-of-enterprise-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2006 21:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/01/05/the-future-of-enterprise-software/</guid>
      <description>There have been many blog postings over the past two weeks making technology predictions for 2006 and beyond. Bill Burnham has taken a look back at 2005 and sees that the software industry itself has been shrinking. Last year, the aggregate market capitalization of the software sector shank by almost 10%.
From this he makes some very interesting predictions which are very close to what we have been hearing anecdotally and which are supported by many of the moves in the enterprise space in recent times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source nipping at Business Objects Heels?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/11/08/opensource-nipping-at-business-objects-heels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2005 09:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/11/08/opensource-nipping-at-business-objects-heels/</guid>
      <description>Business Objects have announced that they are joining the Eclipse Foundation and are going to Open Source some of their tools. This is a very timely move for them as there appears to be a lot of energy building behind their Open Source competitors which must surely be hurting sales of Crystal at the low-end.
Whilst none of the Open Source tools have the breadth and depth of Crystal&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, in many cases they are &amp;ldquo;good enough&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aperi - nice idea, but will it fly?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/11/03/aperi-nice-idea-but-will-it-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2005 10:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/11/03/aperi-nice-idea-but-will-it-fly/</guid>
      <description>Jon William Toigo over at Byte &amp;amp; Switchhas a great article on Aperi and the history of SRM in general. His analysis of industry reaction to the Aperi announcement by IBM is particularly incisive.
Whether IBM will succeed (with the help of the OpenSource community) or not is obviously the great unknown. In any other sector the chances would be good but so many initiatives in this area have started with grand hopes and ended up as yet another niche product optimised for a small set of specific hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMDB Plateau of Productivity 10 years out?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/10/25/cmdb-plateau-of-productivity-10-years-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2005 10:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/10/25/cmdb-plateau-of-productivity-10-years-out/</guid>
      <description>The Register has a pointed article on the BMC SORM (Service Oriented Resource Management) announcements. Further into the article they quote Gartner as saying, in its &amp;ldquo;Hype Cycle for IT Operations Management, 2005&amp;rdquo; that CMDBs are at the &amp;ldquo;peak of inflated expectations&amp;rdquo; with the &amp;ldquo;plateau of productivity&amp;rdquo; some 10 years out.
Whilst it does appear that CMDBs are all the rage right now and that inflated expectations will (as ever) lead to half-baked solutions and disappointed customers, we have seen plenty of benefit being gained right now in the implementation of limited scope CMDBs targetted at particular technology-business relationships in IT Service Management and Delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise IT - really dying?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/10/06/enterprise-it-really-dying/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2005 12:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/10/06/enterprise-it-really-dying/</guid>
      <description>Chip Hazard on Jeff Bussgang&amp;rsquo;s Blog has a great riposte to the assertion that the Enterprise software business is dying. In particular, his first point about driving IT efficiency is very relevant to our business area.
We spend most of our time developing custom solutions for clients who have made large up-front investments in enterprise applications and now want to maximise the return on that investment. In some case, this may simply be a case of extracting out data in a summary form from these systems so that they can make informed planning decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting without implementing</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/09/26/consulting-without-implementing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2005 13:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/09/26/consulting-without-implementing/</guid>
      <description>There is an interview over on Steve Shu&amp;rsquo;s Blog with Mike McLaughlin, a Management Consultant from Deloitte. Whilst the bulk of the interview is targetted at MBA students, there is one very telling comment about executable strategies rather than credenza-ware. Surprisingly, there are still many large Consultancies out there with no delivery capability. They can guide you on an IT strategy but they have no ability to help you implement it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look who&#39;s laughing now</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/08/23/look-whos-laughing-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2005 11:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/08/23/look-whos-laughing-now/</guid>
      <description>CNET hasa very good interview with Bernard Liautaud who is Chief Executive of Business Objects. His vision for Business Intelligence has enabled BO to grow at an impressive rate. Whilst we can criticise the technical support problems which have occurred in the Crystal product range since they acquired Crystal Decisions, we have been mightily impressed by how smoothly the product integration has gone.
The points regarding competition from Microsoft are not particularly well made by the interviewer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if VisiCalc had been patented?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/08/14/what-if-visicalc-had-been-patented/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2005 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/08/14/what-if-visicalc-had-been-patented/</guid>
      <description>The whole issue of Software Patents has been a hot potato recently. We intend doing some postings on it in the near future but in the meantime, Dan Brinklin has a very thought-provoking article regarding patents, VisiCalc, Microsoft and the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
