<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FoWA on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/fowa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FoWA on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 18:33:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/fowa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>If you pass on DemoBar you can never complain again</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/if-you-pass-on-demobar-you-can-never-complain-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 18:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/if-you-pass-on-demobar-you-can-never-complain-again/</guid>
      <description>OK here&amp;rsquo;s the deal.
On Thursday September 13th, an event called DemoBar is being held. This is a chance for 10 web startups to demo their product to an audience consisting of their peers, the press, Irish investors, UK investors, Enterprise Ireland, the Future of WebApps conference organisers and a bunch of other people.
Not only that but we&amp;rsquo;ll be announcing shortly on the Web2Ireland.org site that EI is arranging for a pitch training session that afternoon for both Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley attendees and DemoBar participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web2Ireland Week in Dublin looks awesome</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2007 19:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</guid>
      <description>Look at the lineup (form Web2Ireland.org blog):
 Mashup University - Monday 10th/Tuesday 11th Mashup Camp - Wednesday 12th/Thursday 13th Paddy’s Valley Meet-up- Thursday 13th DemoBar and FOWA Road trip - Thursday 13th OpenCoffee - Friday 14th  The Mashup Camp and Uni really looks like a wonderful four days. Only €25 nominal sign-up to learn a ton of stuff. If you are a developer and you are not attending at least one day of this, you missing out on something special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoWA MP3s and Presentations now available</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/fowa-mp3s-and-presentations-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 22:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/fowa-mp3s-and-presentations-now-available/</guid>
      <description>The good people of Carson Systems have made the recordings and presentations of the various speakers from FoWA London 2007 available for download. Even though I was there I&amp;rsquo;ve grabbed a bunch of them to listen to and read again as there are some real gems. If only other conference organisers were so generous!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoWA Day2, part 2</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/fowa-day2-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 14:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/fowa-day2-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Back at base now and didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance yesterday to write about some of the other speakers. Overall Day 1 was more impressive than Day 2. The Open Mic slot was poor overall but Phil&amp;rsquo;s presentation was very entertaining. It was a pity he had so little time as I&amp;rsquo;m sure a Q&amp;amp;A; afterwards would have been very heated!
However we did have another highlight near the end with the guys from MOO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggestion for FON</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/suggestion-for-fon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/suggestion-for-fon/</guid>
      <description>Given the lack of free wireless at FoWA and the disastrous wireless at LeWeb3, it struck me yesterday that conferences are the ideal opportunity for FON to give people real hands-on experience of their routers.
Imagine if the guys had provided all the wifi for free yesterday? They could still use the logon screens so they get the branding opportunities but it would have been such a coup! Maybe an idea for some of the upcoming European conferences?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoWA Day 2</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Adobe pitch about Flex etc. Not my cup of tea.
Chris Wilson from the IE7 team. Excellent honest presentation on why they lost their way with IE. Mentioned microformats so my ears pricked up. RSS in IE7 - he&amp;rsquo;s very excited by this. I really think it&amp;rsquo;ll push the uptake of using RSS. Chris just went through all the changes in IE7 and is now going through some of the newer MS Web tools including the free ones and the VPC image with IE6 in it so you can test both IE7 and IE6 on the same machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoWA Day 1 - Seriously Good</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-1-seriously-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/fowa-day-1-seriously-good/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s often said about conferences that you don&amp;rsquo;t go for the speakers, you go for the networking. However, yesterday at FoWA had some of the finest presentations I have seen in the past twelve months. I ended the day buzzing with ideas for LouderVoice. Sure there was some misfires but overall Ryan had a very successful day on his hands.
Highlights for me were: * Mike Arrington - Just good solid stuff and well able to handle all the questions thrown at him (except for the Adobe Apollo ones) * Ben Holmes from Index Ventures - Loved this presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan on Outsourcing</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/19/ryan-on-outsourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2007 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/19/ryan-on-outsourcing/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Carson has a good post on outsourcing in the context of DropSend and Amigo. I like his metrics on when to know you are in trouble. His Russian approach is interesting but as he points out, you have to know someone who knows the local scene to do it comfortably.
I&amp;rsquo;ll update our progress here with outsourcing with part three in our series (part 1, part 2) when I get back from FoWA.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
