<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>enterprise ireland on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/enterprise-ireland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in enterprise ireland on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/enterprise-ireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our 2009 Predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</guid>
      <description>The 2008 predictions weren&amp;rsquo;t the most accurate. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how we do for 2009.
 The Android platform will be absolutely huge. With Motorola, Sony Ericsson and a raft of Tier 2 manufacturers signed up, it will become _the _mobile platform from the mid to high end. Ignore the HTC G1, that&amp;rsquo;s just a rough first attempt by one manufacturer.  Despite Android, iPhone will remain big. There is always that 10% of the market who like paying extra for &amp;ldquo;luxury&amp;rdquo; brands SaaS ecommerce providers will go mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A word of thanks</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 14:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</guid>
      <description>Founders of start-ups tend to spend a lot of time griping about things. I could write an essay on how it took from Aug 28th to Dec 3rd for Enterprise Ireland to issue a document needed to get us BES approval. Instead I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the positive part of that story.
On Dec 3rd, EI shuffled the paperwork-exercise out the door and it arrived in the Revenue Commissioners. Our solicitors also submitted our RICT outline application around the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pitch Videos from Irish Start-Ups In Palo Alto</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/12/06/pitch-videos-from-irish-start-ups-in-palo-alto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 11:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/12/06/pitch-videos-from-irish-start-ups-in-palo-alto/</guid>
      <description>The Enterprise Ireland and InterTradeIreland VC Forum pitching event in Silicon Valley on Tuesday looks to have been a great event. Five Irish web start-ups pitched to a panel of local VCs and an invited audience. You can see all the videos over at the Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley blog. The really interesting part for me was the questions from the VCs. They have a very strong focus on competitive advantage. It&amp;rsquo;s well worth your time watching all five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New BES limits OKed by EU!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just heard (via Joe Drumgoole&amp;rsquo;s blog) that the new BES limits annnounced last November have finally been approved by the EU. This is fantastic news.
This is the official EU newsletter announcement:
Notification or Registration Date:	23.05.2007 DG Responsible:	Competition DG Related Procedures:	N 311 / 2004
Decision on 23.08.2007:	Article 4§3 - decision not to raise objections
This presumably means that Enterprise Ireland should be processing new company certs starting five days ago and the Revenue Commissioners should be approving RICTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paddy&#39;s Valley in the Press</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/30/paddys-valley-in-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 10:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/30/paddys-valley-in-the-press/</guid>
      <description>The Irish Times has covered the latest press release about our Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley trip. The support of Enterprise Ireland in not just important but it is really getting noticed by the press. Finfacts also give us a mention and I was interviewed by Cork 103FM and ENN. There are still plenty of places left but we will be setting a cut-off date soon so head on over to the site, read all about it, ask questions, make comments and then sign up if you like the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is EI refusing to do any pre-work for BES?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2007 10:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</guid>
      <description>As anyone who has kicked off a BES scheme knows there are a few simple steps you have to do in order to qualify. The key one is a &amp;ldquo;New Company Cert&amp;rdquo; from Enterprise Ireland or a CEB. To qualify for the cert they generally give you a small employment grant (a Feasibility Study Grant is not sufficient). You can then go to the Revenue and start the actual BES process itself and get in-principal approval for your scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll-on Curry 2.1</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/roll-on-curry-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/roll-on-curry-21/</guid>
      <description>Paul Walsh&amp;rsquo;s Curry 2.0 was held last night in Jaipur in Dublin and was stonkingly good. A great mix of people from different backgrounds spent the night talking about tech, business and naan.
I started badly by sitting down next to someone and asking them if they were with Microsoft, given that they were wearing a blue monster t-shirt. It turned out to be Dennis Howlett (Accman) who took great good-humoured umbrage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Desking and Incubation Centres in Cork</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/09/hot-desking-and-incubation-centres-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 08:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/09/hot-desking-and-incubation-centres-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a great meeting with Paul Healy of the Rubicon Incubation Centre in CIT in Cork. This has been a runaway success since it opened a year ago and I wanted to find out more. The Centre is probably best know for the Genesis Enterprise Programme but actually offers a lot more than this.
The Centre has not had a lot of marketing around it and I wondered why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interest in a Cork OpenCoffee Club meetup next week?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 22:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Starting with Saul in London followed quickly by Eoghan in Dublin and James/Jan in Limerick, it looks like the OpenCoffee Club idea really does have legs. The core idea is that a regular informal meeting is held in a coffee shop where we try to bring together entrepreneurs and investors to discuss topics of mutual interest, learn from each other and hopefully build lasting business relationships over time.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to propose an inaugural one in Cork City for next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must-read post over at the itnorthwest Blog</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 19:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</guid>
      <description>Julian Ellison from Tablane has written the best summary of startup funding, finance and the Irish economy that I have ever read. I have one small contribution to make on it. He mentions the Business Angels Partnership and wonders how they &amp;ldquo;market&amp;rdquo; ideas that they receive.
I highly recommend that anyone with a strong well-thought out business plan just contact them and talk to them face to face. The basic way they work is that they help people who come in with strong ideas to ensure that the idea has legs and that some basic financial analysis and planning has been done.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
