<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web20 on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/web20/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web20 on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 12:56:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/web20/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>blognation Ireland Launches</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/13/blognation-ireland-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/13/blognation-ireland-launches/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m still buzzing over the fact that the blognation Ireland site has gone live. We&amp;rsquo;ve already made it to the front page of Techmeme!
As I said in the opening post:
The Irish site is part of the blognation network which is building up to be the biggest tech news site on non-US Web 2.0 startups around the globe including EMEA, Asia-Pacific, Latin America and Canada
Feel free to send me any news about your web or mobile application, no matter how early stage you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendations for Web Application Development shops?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2006 11:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</guid>
      <description>We intend to outsource the bulk of the development of our application. This will be broken down into several areas including:
 Design XHTML/CSS Application development Hosting Operations  I have received plenty of recommendations for Design and some for XHTML/CSS but other than Ryan Carson recommending Nick in Plum Digital Media (and more on yesterday&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;How to build a WebApp&amp;rdquo; workshop later), it is proving difficult to get recommendations for top-class web application development houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Q&amp;A and final comment</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-qa-and-final-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 18:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-qa-and-final-comment/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 5 out of 5
The Q&amp;amp;A; session didn&amp;rsquo;t last very long but did throw up some interesting points.
To kick off, there were various tech questions for Rob. Then Fergus was asked how long it took to launch Nooked, He replied that it was about a year after 3 different models. Walter was asked how he was hiring. He isn&amp;rsquo;t. There was a question about to get the right right developer expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Rob Burke</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-rob-burke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 16:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-rob-burke/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
As sponsers of the conference, it was only fair that Microsoft was given the opportunity to present their Web 2.0 wares. I talked to Rob the previous night to discover that he is an evangelist from Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Platform and Developer Group. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of this type of role within companies. Good evangelists can transform the image of a company and really re-invigorate employees as I believe Robert Scoble has done for Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Walter Higgins</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-walter-higgins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 15:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-walter-higgins/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
For out and out geekful rapture, Walter&amp;rsquo;s presentation was a joy. I think it was a very necessary presentation to give (and provided a very nice counter-point to Rob&amp;rsquo;s which followed). There is a perception I think, particularly amongst a lot of the Web 2.0 tech press who appear to have no technical background, that creating a new Ajaxian WebApp is a weekends work mashing a few libraries and services together and alakazamm, it just works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Fergus Burns</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-fergus-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 13:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-fergus-burns/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
I met Fergus for the first time at the EI Web 2.0 Conference back in April but his reputation far preceded him. He has been described as the consummate networker but I think this does him an injustice - he is not just a genuine friendly guy, he is a doer. Whilst have the tech world talks about Web 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Salim Ismail</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-salim-ismail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-salim-ismail/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 5 out of 5
Salim gave a suberb presentation which for me, as expected, was the highlight of the conference. I have heard chunks of the presentation on various Podcasts and it is still very focused on the ideas they built in PubSub despite the fact that Salim left there several months back. But given that those ideas remain as relevant now as they were when PubSub was founded, the presentation was compelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Shel Israel</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-shel-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 09:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-shel-israel/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 3 out of 5
Shel Israel was the first to talk and really pitched the presentation at those who knew little about Web 2.0 or blogging. The bulk of the presentation was built around the themes in the book he wrote with Robert Scoble (Naked Conversations). Some of the shows of hands during the various talks indicated that he could probably have moved the level up a notch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Review Intro</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-review-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 09:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-review-intro/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 5 out of 5
Tom, Catherine and all the team at IT@Cork put on a fantastic half day Web 2.0 conference on Thursday.
The geek dinner the night before set the scene perfectly - thanks again to Damien and all the organisers of that and Stormhoek for the wine. I finally got to meet Damien, Donncha, Gavin and a few others who I had previously only known through their blogs like Branedy and his lovely wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web 2.0 Conference Dublin - much food for thought</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/04/30/web-20-conference-dublin-much-food-for-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2006 09:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/04/30/web-20-conference-dublin-much-food-for-thought/</guid>
      <description>The Web 2.0 Conference in Dublin was a big success and was well worth attending. It was great to finally put faces to a lot of names in the Irish tech world and beyond. I went out the previous night to an informal meet-up arranged by Robert Smith. The layout of the place unfortunately was not conducive to talking to lots of the people who turned up which meant I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to talk to Marc Canter about Microformats and Structured Blogging until the following day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
