<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CEB on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/ceb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CEB on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:09:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/ceb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IIA Congress Discounts</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/28/iia-congress-discounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/28/iia-congress-discounts/</guid>
      <description>West Cork Enterprise Board contacted me last week to let me know about a discount offer they had received from the IIA for their client companies (and those of all CEBs). There was a further discount offered for being outside of Dublin too. Whilst the original price of €345 for non-members was just a bit at the high end for us, the double-discounted price of less than €150 is a bargain and I&amp;rsquo;ve signed up to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Small/Micro Businesses and the web</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/08/irish-smallmicro-businesses-and-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 15:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/08/irish-smallmicro-businesses-and-the-web/</guid>
      <description>A recurring conversation I have had recently is around very small non-technical Irish businesses having a web presence. I do a lot of Tech-Checks for the Cork CEBs and I continue to be surprised by how many of these businesses are invisible online.
One of the reasons for this may be that companies still think it costs a lot of money to have a web-site and non eircom.net email addresses. And there are still gougers out there charging people €2k for a simple off-the-shelf brochure site with stock graphics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is EI refusing to do any pre-work for BES?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2007 10:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</guid>
      <description>As anyone who has kicked off a BES scheme knows there are a few simple steps you have to do in order to qualify. The key one is a &amp;ldquo;New Company Cert&amp;rdquo; from Enterprise Ireland or a CEB. To qualify for the cert they generally give you a small employment grant (a Feasibility Study Grant is not sufficient). You can then go to the Revenue and start the actual BES process itself and get in-principal approval for your scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interest in a Cork OpenCoffee Club meetup next week?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 22:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Starting with Saul in London followed quickly by Eoghan in Dublin and James/Jan in Limerick, it looks like the OpenCoffee Club idea really does have legs. The core idea is that a regular informal meeting is held in a coffee shop where we try to bring together entrepreneurs and investors to discuss topics of mutual interest, learn from each other and hopefully build lasting business relationships over time.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to propose an inaugural one in Cork City for next week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
