<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>entrepreneurship on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in entrepreneurship on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2007 21:06:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Leader Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/05/itcork-leader-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2007 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/05/itcork-leader-awards/</guid>
      <description>This is such a great idea.
On November 1, 2007 it@cork will have their first ever Leader’s Awards. They want to recognise some of the leading companies and individuals in the community and have an evening of networking, reflection and celebration.
There are 4 categories:
 1. Emerging Company Award - to recognise a leading company in early stage business planning and execution 2. High Potential Award - to recognise a leading established company driving forward in international markets 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get an Irish David Heinemeier Hansson</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/how-to-get-an-irish-david-heinemeier-hansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 13:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/how-to-get-an-irish-david-heinemeier-hansson/</guid>
      <description>We have a deep rooted problem in Ireland with getting young people to take part in the start-up culture. Every kid who leaves college with a degree in engineering/computing/business in the US wants to build something great. Every kid who leaves college in Ireland with a degree in engineering/computing/business wants a nice job in a bank or multi-national. This has to change.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been interviewing people for many years in all my different jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Start-up culture Panel at FoWA</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Carson - Carson Systems, Richard Moross - Moo, Mike Arrington - TechCrunch, Mike Butcher - Vecosys, Chris Messina - Citizen Agency, Saul Klein - Index Ventures, Max Jennings - eMomentum, Colin Donald - Futurescape, Tariq Krim - NetVibes. * Richard - Afraid of failure in Europe * Mike A - Stop talking and start doing, if we want to be like Silicon Valley. Smart people move to Silicon Valley which is a big help * Mike B - Subject is 18 months out of date.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
