<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>funding on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/funding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in funding on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 15:21:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/funding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising Discussion on The Last Word</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, I was on TodayFM&amp;rsquo;s The Last Word radio show with Professor Frank Roche talking to Matt Cooper. The topic was centered on fund raising in the current economic climate. You can hear what we had to say in this audio clip. The interview starts about 4 minutes 30 seconds in.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that our 2008 BES offering is open until Dec 31st. The response to-date has been very positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeedCamp Launches - apply now!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</guid>
      <description>At the Essential Web conference last week Saul Klein announced SeedCamp. This is an incredibly important initiative that will help grow the spirit of entrepreneurship across Europe. It basically takes a YCombinator type model and implements it here.
For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, YCombinator is hugely successful project of Paul Graham in the US. Twice a year, once in Boston, once in SV, they ask (pre)startups to apply for a slot on the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at Essential Web 07</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/loudervoice-at-essential-web-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 09:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/loudervoice-at-essential-web-07/</guid>
      <description>We sent out this press release yesterday:
The purpose of the event is to provide a picture of the status and temperature of the web scene in Europe. The sessions will have a mix of upcoming and hot web companies - some will be pre-funded, raw start-ups, others will be well-funded and well-known.
&amp;ldquo;This as an incredible opportunity for us to attract further funding from world-class investors.&amp;rdquo; said CEO, Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s how to do it</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/12/heres-how-to-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2007 13:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/12/heres-how-to-do-it/</guid>
      <description>Go, read Ben Barren&amp;rsquo;s post on &amp;quot; Who Will Fund Local Web 2.0 Aussie Businesses?&amp;quot; and replace Australia everywhere with Ireland.
It&amp;rsquo;s a simple formula, I believe it can work.
Anything is better than where we are right now. When your VC activity is mentioned in the same sentence as Romania, you know you have a deep deep problem to solve.
A report onour visit to London Open Coffee coming later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Start-up culture Panel at FoWA</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Carson - Carson Systems, Richard Moross - Moo, Mike Arrington - TechCrunch, Mike Butcher - Vecosys, Chris Messina - Citizen Agency, Saul Klein - Index Ventures, Max Jennings - eMomentum, Colin Donald - Futurescape, Tariq Krim - NetVibes. * Richard - Afraid of failure in Europe * Mike A - Stop talking and start doing, if we want to be like Silicon Valley. Smart people move to Silicon Valley which is a big help * Mike B - Subject is 18 months out of date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from BarCampIreland SouthEast starting to appear</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</guid>
      <description>Keith has uploaded videos of the &amp;ldquo;Finding money for your start-up&amp;rdquo; session. I enjoyed the differing views of the panel on this topic but anyone who thought they&amp;rsquo;d come away with &amp;ldquo;so that&amp;rsquo;s how I do it&amp;rdquo; would have been disappointed. There should definitely be a follow-up session at BarCamp Dublin with a focus on successful early-stage tech startup fund-raising.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
