<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rubicon on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/rubicon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rubicon on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 15:37:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/rubicon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Joining Genesis Enterprise Programme</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/30/joining-genesis-enterprise-programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 15:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/30/joining-genesis-enterprise-programme/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re really excited at Argolon HQ to announce that we&amp;rsquo;ve been accepted on to the Genesis Enterprise Programme. We&amp;rsquo;ve had lots of dealings with both the Rubicon Centre and GEP over the past year through Cork OpenCoffee and have been thoroughly impressed with the whole operation.
I&amp;rsquo;ve presented LouderVoice to Denise Kennedy, who runs GEP, twice over the past 18 months. I can honestly say it didn&amp;rsquo;t go well the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee now fully blogified</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/01/cork-opencoffee-now-fully-blogified/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 10:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/01/cork-opencoffee-now-fully-blogified/</guid>
      <description>The disaster that was the information site about Cork OpenCoffee has finally been resolved. No more re-directs to Upcoming or Eventful. We now have a nice clean blog which you can subscribe to via RSS or email. We&amp;rsquo;ll keep it fully up to date with everything that is happening in OCC here.
If you have anything you want to share with the group, use any of the contacts methods listed on the site to send it through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Desking and Incubation Centres in Cork</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/09/hot-desking-and-incubation-centres-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 08:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/09/hot-desking-and-incubation-centres-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a great meeting with Paul Healy of the Rubicon Incubation Centre in CIT in Cork. This has been a runaway success since it opened a year ago and I wanted to find out more. The Centre is probably best know for the Genesis Enterprise Programme but actually offers a lot more than this.
The Centre has not had a lot of marketing around it and I wondered why.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
