<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BarCampIreland on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/barcampireland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BarCampIreland on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 15:44:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/barcampireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork III Next Weekend</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/11/07/barcamp-cork-iii-next-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 15:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/11/07/barcamp-cork-iii-next-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As co-organiser of the first two Cork BarCamps, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to see the third one is happening next Saturday 14th Nov in the fabulous Cork International Airport Hotel. The able organisers this time around are Gordon Murray, Ciara Crossan and Ciara Feely.
BarCamp is one of those free conferences where you leave having gained far more from the day than you expect. It&amp;rsquo;s the serendipity that makes it special. I have built many friendships and business relationships with the people I meet there over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork II on November 1st</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/30/barcamp-cork-ii-on-november-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 08:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/30/barcamp-cork-ii-on-november-1st/</guid>
      <description>It has been over two years since the last one, but BarCamp is finally coming back to Cork. It&amp;rsquo;s soon, very soon, only four weeks away. The venue is the lovely Webworks building in the City Centre, just like the last time.
We have a strong vision for this event and we need your help to make it happen on the day. Please read the first set of posts and give us your feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCampDublin Today</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/21/barcampdublin-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2007 07:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/21/barcampdublin-today/</guid>
      <description>Hope you all have an amazing day and shake things up a bit!
Sorry I can&amp;rsquo;t make it this time. Next time I promise.
If you are in Dublin today, head on over to the Digital Hub to see the future of conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content and Convergence</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/17/content-and-convergence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 19:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/17/content-and-convergence/</guid>
      <description>Haydn has offered up some quite controversial opinions on where many Irish web companies should put their energies and also what the BarCampDublin focus should be. It&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;d like to see argued from both points of view so please head over to Mediangler and offer your thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Dublin coming on April 21st</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/12/barcamp-dublin-coming-on-april-21st/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 14:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/12/barcamp-dublin-coming-on-april-21st/</guid>
      <description>Elly and the gang have been hard at work putting together BarCamp Dublin and it looks like a winner. This is the third one after Cork and Waterford and I love the look of the speaker line-up. If you are free at all on Saturday week I&amp;rsquo;d encourage you to head over. Do sign-up so they know how many people to expect.
Some of the talks that catch my eye include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from BarCampIreland SouthEast starting to appear</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</guid>
      <description>Keith has uploaded videos of the &amp;ldquo;Finding money for your start-up&amp;rdquo; session. I enjoyed the differing views of the panel on this topic but anyone who thought they&amp;rsquo;d come away with &amp;ldquo;so that&amp;rsquo;s how I do it&amp;rdquo; would have been disappointed. There should definitely be a follow-up session at BarCamp Dublin with a focus on successful early-stage tech startup fund-raising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice decloaking today</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/23/loudervoice-decloaking-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 09:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/23/loudervoice-decloaking-today/</guid>
      <description>I was very open about what we&amp;rsquo;re up to in LouderVoice at BarcampIreland South East on Saturday and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure it was videoed so there is no point in remaining coy. We&amp;rsquo;ll update the main sign-up page with more information and I&amp;rsquo;ll blog it over at the LouderVoice blog later today.
Technorati Tags: loudervoice, argolon, barcamp, barcampireland, barcampirelandsoutheast</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos of Donncha&#39;s Wordpress talk at BarCamp Ireland South East</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/22/videos-of-donnchas-wordpress-talk-at-barcamp-ireland-south-east/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 16:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/22/videos-of-donnchas-wordpress-talk-at-barcamp-ireland-south-east/</guid>
      <description>I compressed them a lot to reduce upload time on ADSL but the sound quality is ok.
The first segment is all about Wordpress itself:
The second has more on Wordpress but also a lot on working in a global virtual team and working from home:
Both well worth viewing.
Technorati Tags: wordpress, wordpress+mu, donncha+o+caoimh, barcamp, barcampireland, barcampirelandsoutheast</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another memorable Irish BarCamp</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/22/another-memorable-irish-barcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 10:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/22/another-memorable-irish-barcamp/</guid>
      <description>The second Irish BarCamp was thoroughly enjoyable and I&amp;rsquo;m already looking forward to the next one.  Review of Event &#39;BarCamp Ireland South East&#39; 04:09 on Jan 22 2007 by Argolon Solutions Team  4
 ![](http://beta.loudervoice.com/static/images/small-star.png)  Keith, Tom and the gang organised a great conference on Saturday and once again, everyone left with their heads buzzing with ideas and plans.
I drove Damien and Tom Atkins from Cork and we arrived at 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Ireland South-East coming Q1 &#39;07</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/11/18/barcamp-ireland-south-east-coming-q1-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2006 12:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/11/18/barcamp-ireland-south-east-coming-q1-07/</guid>
      <description>Keith has the details. It&amp;rsquo;ll be held in WIT in Waterford. I&amp;rsquo;ll definitely be there. Blog here. Wiki here. Go and sign yourself up.
Technorati Tags: BarCamp, BarCampIrelandSouthEast</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
