<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/investment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 15:21:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/investment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising Discussion on The Last Word</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, I was on TodayFM&amp;rsquo;s The Last Word radio show with Professor Frank Roche talking to Matt Cooper. The topic was centered on fund raising in the current economic climate. You can hear what we had to say in this audio clip. The interview starts about 4 minutes 30 seconds in.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that our 2008 BES offering is open until Dec 31st. The response to-date has been very positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoiltchild looking for advice</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/10/29/spoiltchild-looking-for-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 22:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/10/29/spoiltchild-looking-for-advice/</guid>
      <description>Good post from Alan of Spoiltchild wondering about their investment strategy for Toddle and future apps. If you have any knowledge in this area, why not head over and leave a comment?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New BES limits OKed by EU!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just heard (via Joe Drumgoole&amp;rsquo;s blog) that the new BES limits annnounced last November have finally been approved by the EU. This is fantastic news.
This is the official EU newsletter announcement:
Notification or Registration Date:	23.05.2007 DG Responsible:	Competition DG Related Procedures:	N 311 / 2004
Decision on 23.08.2007:	Article 4ยง3 - decision not to raise objections
This presumably means that Enterprise Ireland should be processing new company certs starting five days ago and the Revenue Commissioners should be approving RICTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limerick OCC Livestream and Auctomatic Interview</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/09/limerick-occ-livestream-and-auctomatic-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 12:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/09/limerick-occ-livestream-and-auctomatic-interview/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not often that people and technology come together so brilliantly as this morning&amp;rsquo;s Limerick OpenCoffee. I&amp;rsquo;ve just taken part in their regular session whilst sitting in a kitchen in Wexford.
Conn O Muineachain livestreamed the entire event using Ustream.tv so anyone could logon and see what was happening whilst a chat-channel allowed us to interact with the attendees. Some backchannel stuff on Twitter and Jaiku added to the mix. If that&amp;rsquo;s all they had done, then it rates as a great success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeedCamp Launches - apply now!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</guid>
      <description>At the Essential Web conference last week Saul Klein announced SeedCamp. This is an incredibly important initiative that will help grow the spirit of entrepreneurship across Europe. It basically takes a YCombinator type model and implements it here.
For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, YCombinator is hugely successful project of Paul Graham in the US. Twice a year, once in Boston, once in SV, they ask (pre)startups to apply for a slot on the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at Essential Web 07</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/loudervoice-at-essential-web-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 09:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/loudervoice-at-essential-web-07/</guid>
      <description>We sent out this press release yesterday:
The purpose of the event is to provide a picture of the status and temperature of the web scene in Europe. The sessions will have a mix of upcoming and hot web companies - some will be pre-funded, raw start-ups, others will be well-funded and well-known.
&amp;ldquo;This as an incredible opportunity for us to attract further funding from world-class investors.&amp;rdquo; said CEO, Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s how to do it</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/12/heres-how-to-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2007 13:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/12/heres-how-to-do-it/</guid>
      <description>Go, read Ben Barren&amp;rsquo;s post on &amp;quot; Who Will Fund Local Web 2.0 Aussie Businesses?&amp;quot; and replace Australia everywhere with Ireland.
It&amp;rsquo;s a simple formula, I believe it can work.
Anything is better than where we are right now. When your VC activity is mentioned in the same sentence as Romania, you know you have a deep deep problem to solve.
A report onour visit to London Open Coffee coming later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good news from the EU</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/09/good-news-from-the-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2007 10:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/09/good-news-from-the-eu/</guid>
      <description>My blood can stop boiling now. The EU has turned down the objection regarding the new BES scheme by the employment-haters in the ICTU. This should accelerate the overall approval process and enable us to hire staff and build a profitable company which contributes to the exchequer and Irish economy in multiple ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from BarCampIreland SouthEast starting to appear</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</guid>
      <description>Keith has uploaded videos of the &amp;ldquo;Finding money for your start-up&amp;rdquo; session. I enjoyed the differing views of the panel on this topic but anyone who thought they&amp;rsquo;d come away with &amp;ldquo;so that&amp;rsquo;s how I do it&amp;rdquo; would have been disappointed. There should definitely be a follow-up session at BarCamp Dublin with a focus on successful early-stage tech startup fund-raising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must-read post over at the itnorthwest Blog</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 19:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</guid>
      <description>Julian Ellison from Tablane has written the best summary of startup funding, finance and the Irish economy that I have ever read. I have one small contribution to make on it. He mentions the Business Angels Partnership and wonders how they &amp;ldquo;market&amp;rdquo; ideas that they receive.
I highly recommend that anyone with a strong well-thought out business plan just contact them and talk to them face to face. The basic way they work is that they help people who come in with strong ideas to ensure that the idea has legs and that some basic financial analysis and planning has been done.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
