<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Outsourcing on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/outsourcing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Outsourcing on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2007 14:25:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/outsourcing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From India back to Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/25/from-india-back-to-silicon-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2007 14:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/25/from-india-back-to-silicon-valley/</guid>
      <description>I have huge respect for Munjal Shah of Riya and I was pretty gob-smacked to read his most recent blog post announcing that they are shutting their Bangalore office and centralising all development in Silicon Valley. His reasons are compelling, particularly for a start-up, even a well funded one.
When we started our outsourcing search last July, we were open to getting the work done anywhere. I&amp;rsquo;d just had some good experiences in working with remote teams in China and India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan on Outsourcing</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/19/ryan-on-outsourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2007 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/19/ryan-on-outsourcing/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Carson has a good post on outsourcing in the context of DropSend and Amigo. I like his metrics on when to know you are in trouble. His Russian approach is interesting but as he points out, you have to know someone who knows the local scene to do it comfortably.
I&amp;rsquo;ll update our progress here with outsourcing with part three in our series (part 1, part 2) when I get back from FoWA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendations for Web Application Development shops?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2006 11:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</guid>
      <description>We intend to outsource the bulk of the development of our application. This will be broken down into several areas including:
 Design XHTML/CSS Application development Hosting Operations  I have received plenty of recommendations for Design and some for XHTML/CSS but other than Ryan Carson recommending Nick in Plum Digital Media (and more on yesterday&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;How to build a WebApp&amp;rdquo; workshop later), it is proving difficult to get recommendations for top-class web application development houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use of Scrum with outsourcers?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/14/use-of-scrum-with-outsourcers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2006 07:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/14/use-of-scrum-with-outsourcers/</guid>
      <description>Over the many years I have worked in project management I have become less and less a fan of the highly formalised methodologies and much more impressed by Agile approaches. I have seen more death marches driven by gantts than I care to remember. In fact, I saw one in Lucent many years ago that took MS Project over five minutes to load due to the number of dependencies they were trying to track.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
