<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web20 on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/web20/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web20 on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:54:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/web20/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nooked makes advertising personal</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/06/nooked-makes-advertising-personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/06/nooked-makes-advertising-personal/</guid>
      <description>The fundamental problem with advertising is that it has always taken the shotgun approach. Show the same ad to as many people as possible and hope some of them like it. Systems like Google AdSense have improved things a lot by showing ads related to the content on a web-page but they are still not ideal and give the person who owns the web-page minimal control beyond some simple competitor-exclusions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web2Ireland Week in Dublin looks awesome</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2007 19:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</guid>
      <description>Look at the lineup (form Web2Ireland.org blog):
 Mashup University - Monday 10th/Tuesday 11th Mashup Camp - Wednesday 12th/Thursday 13th Paddy’s Valley Meet-up- Thursday 13th DemoBar and FOWA Road trip - Thursday 13th OpenCoffee - Friday 14th  The Mashup Camp and Uni really looks like a wonderful four days. Only €25 nominal sign-up to learn a ton of stuff. If you are a developer and you are not attending at least one day of this, you missing out on something special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blognation Ireland Launches</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/13/blognation-ireland-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/13/blognation-ireland-launches/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m still buzzing over the fact that the blognation Ireland site has gone live. We&amp;rsquo;ve already made it to the front page of Techmeme!
As I said in the opening post:
The Irish site is part of the blognation network which is building up to be the biggest tech news site on non-US Web 2.0 startups around the globe including EMEA, Asia-Pacific, Latin America and Canada
Feel free to send me any news about your web or mobile application, no matter how early stage you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like to present your webapp to 5000 people?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/10/like-to-present-your-webapp-to-5000-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2007 13:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/10/like-to-present-your-webapp-to-5000-people/</guid>
      <description>Web 2.0 Expo is coming to Berlin from 5th-8th November and it is a serious opportunity for those involved in web development in Ireland to get noticed.
Jennifer Pahlka, one of the organisers, is coming to Cork on July 14th and Tom Raftery has arranged an OpenDrinks Event that evening for any Irish people interested in going to the Web 2.0 Expo or, more importantly, for anyone hoping to present there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Nokia wake up like they did with paper products?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/will-nokia-wake-up-like-they-did-with-paper-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 13:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/will-nokia-wake-up-like-they-did-with-paper-products/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking recently about Nokia and my general feeling is that they are missing many simple opportunities to retain leadership in mobile development.
Apart from one crappy Panasonic and a dog-slow Sony-Ericcson T610, I&amp;rsquo;ve always used Nokia phones. They have been solid workhorses with just the right combination of features for me. Until last year, that meant Series 40 phones but I then finally succumbed and bought an N70 a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeedCamp Launches - apply now!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</guid>
      <description>At the Essential Web conference last week Saul Klein announced SeedCamp. This is an incredibly important initiative that will help grow the spirit of entrepreneurship across Europe. It basically takes a YCombinator type model and implements it here.
For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, YCombinator is hugely successful project of Paul Graham in the US. Twice a year, once in Boston, once in SV, they ask (pre)startups to apply for a slot on the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll-on Curry 2.1</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/roll-on-curry-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/roll-on-curry-21/</guid>
      <description>Paul Walsh&amp;rsquo;s Curry 2.0 was held last night in Jaipur in Dublin and was stonkingly good. A great mix of people from different backgrounds spent the night talking about tech, business and naan.
I started badly by sitting down next to someone and asking them if they were with Microsoft, given that they were wearing a blue monster t-shirt. It turned out to be Dennis Howlett (Accman) who took great good-humoured umbrage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderMinis now on Jaiku too</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 08:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</guid>
      <description>We announced LouderTweets recently, which are 140 character mini-reviews you can send to LouderVoice from Twitter without needing a LouderVoice account.
Last night we turned on LouderViesti which is the equivalent feature for the superb Jaiku. Jaiku is like Twitter but can do much much more. They are based in Finland and are adding great features at a fast rate.
We are now calling LouderTweets+LouderViesti = LouderMinis!
Using LouderViesti is even easier than LouderTweets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Twitter Mash-Up</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 12:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</guid>
      <description>After a few late nights we&amp;rsquo;re now ready to let you send reviews from Twitter to LouderVoice. We&amp;rsquo;re calling them LouderTweets and they are 140 character mini-reviews you can send using Web, SMS or IM via Twitter to LouderVoice.
An important point is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a LouderVoice member to send LouderTweets but you should join if you want to rate, bookmark and build/share useful collections of reviews and mini-reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote for PollDaddy in the Webware 100</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/11/vote-for-polldaddy-in-the-webware-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 14:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/11/vote-for-polldaddy-in-the-webware-100/</guid>
      <description>Not just because it is a brilliant product but also because Lenny, Jonathan and the guys have shown that small Irish technology companies can have global reach!
These guys pushed out 14 million polls last month and over half of them were non-English-language.
Vote early and often.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
