<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OpenCoffee on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/opencoffee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OpenCoffee on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 16:45:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/opencoffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>West Cork OpenCoffee</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/09/29/west-cork-opencoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 16:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/09/29/west-cork-opencoffee/</guid>
      <description>I founded Cork OpenCoffee back in early 2007 and I&amp;rsquo;m delighted to see it grow to be the most successful OCC in Ireland. The bulk of the organising is now done by Gordon Murray of Murrion Software and Ciara Crossan of Weddingdates.
A few months back OpenCoffee Mallow launched and by all accounts is going really well. Their next meet-up is in Springfort Hall, on Tuesday the 6th of October, from 10 am until approx 12 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenBBQ in Tipperary?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/06/openbbq-in-tipperary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 10:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/06/openbbq-in-tipperary/</guid>
      <description>Cross-posting from the Cork OpenCoffee Blog: What started as a discussion about having an OpenCoffee in the Midlands the other day quickly turned into a proposal for an OpenBBQ in Terryglass on Lough Derg this summer.
Think business networking, free Wifi, top class BBQ and fun.
Evert has all the details so far. Please drop him a line if you think you might go. He’s thinking June/July mid-week. If there is enough interest from Cork OpenCoffee we could consider hiring a mini-bus?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leitrim Business Network</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/16/leitrim-business-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/16/leitrim-business-network/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really pleased to see how well the Leitrim Business Network is taking off. Johnny Beirne from Leitrim CEB and the team are really pushing it forward. I love seeing them evangelise the opportunities presented by online networking through tools like LinkedIn and of course the site itself is a group blog.
it@cork has shown how useful and influential a professional local business network can be, particularly one that understands technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee now fully blogified</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/01/cork-opencoffee-now-fully-blogified/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 10:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/01/cork-opencoffee-now-fully-blogified/</guid>
      <description>The disaster that was the information site about Cork OpenCoffee has finally been resolved. No more re-directs to Upcoming or Eventful. We now have a nice clean blog which you can subscribe to via RSS or email. We&amp;rsquo;ll keep it fully up to date with everything that is happening in OCC here.
If you have anything you want to share with the group, use any of the contacts methods listed on the site to send it through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limerick OCC Livestream and Auctomatic Interview</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/09/limerick-occ-livestream-and-auctomatic-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 12:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/09/limerick-occ-livestream-and-auctomatic-interview/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not often that people and technology come together so brilliantly as this morning&amp;rsquo;s Limerick OpenCoffee. I&amp;rsquo;ve just taken part in their regular session whilst sitting in a kitchen in Wexford.
Conn O Muineachain livestreamed the entire event using Ustream.tv so anyone could logon and see what was happening whilst a chat-channel allowed us to interact with the attendees. Some backchannel stuff on Twitter and Jaiku added to the mix. If that&amp;rsquo;s all they had done, then it rates as a great success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galway OpenCoffee this Friday</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/01/galway-opencoffee-this-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/01/galway-opencoffee-this-friday/</guid>
      <description>Aidan Finn and David Lenehan (aka PollDaddy Lenny) are having an impromptu Galway OCC, Friday 11am Forster Court Hotel. All welcome. Spread the word</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spam-protected eWrite Forms</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/29/spam-protected-ewrite-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 14:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/29/spam-protected-ewrite-forms/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Murray from eWrite is a Cork OpenCoffee stalwart and his eWrite business has been very successful in Ireland. They provide web CMSes and Apps for SMEs. They have put a lot of work into protecting the forms on their customers sites against spam and recently decided to spin this out as a product in itself.
This is one of those simple but extremely useful apps. You can select from a set of forms on the eWrite Forms site and then embed that on your own site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Galway Open Coffee Announced!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/12/first-galway-open-coffee-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 11:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/12/first-galway-open-coffee-announced/</guid>
      <description>Aidan Finn just announced Galway OCC on Twitter. Upcoming.org page here. I&amp;rsquo;d been hoping for this one, I think it&amp;rsquo;ll be a big success. Looking forward to the reports. That plus BarCamp Galway are two great excuses for us to head up there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off to TheNextWeb tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/30/off-to-thenextweb-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 16:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/30/off-to-thenextweb-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m hitting Amsterdam at 5pm tomorrow for both the International OCC and TheNextWeb Conference. I&amp;rsquo;ll demo LouderVoice to as many people as I can and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to the VC Speed Pitching session at lunchtime Friday. I&amp;rsquo;d better practice my elevator pitch tonight.
If you want to contact me from midday Thursday onwards I&amp;rsquo;ll be on +372-53-166646 (roam4free) or +353-87-9790297 (main mobile). I&amp;rsquo;ll be grabbing email on Thursday evening and probably not again until Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Coffee coverage on Read/WriteWeb</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/24/open-coffee-coverage-on-readwriteweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2007 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/24/open-coffee-coverage-on-readwriteweb/</guid>
      <description>David Lenehan has written a great overview of the Open Coffee phenomenon. Cork gets a mention. If you have any interest in building the start-up culture and community in Ireland then it is a must-read. If you like it, please Digg it too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
