<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>it@cork on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/itcork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in it@cork on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 13:59:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/itcork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Annual Conference Announced</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/10/07/itcork-annual-conference-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 13:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/10/07/itcork-annual-conference-announced/</guid>
      <description>The it@cork annual conference has just been announced. Its title is &amp;ldquo;GREEN IT: Reduce CO2, Raise Profits&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s on November 26 in the lovely Radisson SAS Hotel in Cork.
The line-up looks like an excellent mix with the focus being clearly on Green as it relates to IT and Business. I particularly like the profit angle given the turmoil the world is going through right now
The is an Early Bird Discount available – Book on or before October 31 and it&amp;rsquo;s €250 for members, €350 for non members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote in the it@cork Leaders Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/11/vote-in-the-itcork-leaders-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/11/vote-in-the-itcork-leaders-awards/</guid>
      <description>The second annual Leader&amp;rsquo;s Awards are on October 23rd in the Clarion Hotel, Lapps Quay, Cork. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice opportunity to recognise some of the leading companies and individuals in the region.
The winners last year were:
 Emerging Company Award - Cubic Telecom High Potential Award Abtran R&amp;amp;D Project Award - Treemetrics Academic Award - Cork Constraint Computation Centre (4Cs) IT Department Winner - Thomas Crosbie Holdings  Nominations close on September 23rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joining it@cork Steering Committee</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/18/joining-itcork-steering-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 12:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/18/joining-itcork-steering-committee/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really pleased to announce that I&amp;rsquo;ve joined the it@cork steering committee. Since we founded Argolon Solutions, I&amp;rsquo;ve always found it@cork to be the real stand-out organisation nationally. I know other cities would love to replicate its success. It has always managed to strike that balance between meeting the needs of established IT organisations and the needs of start-ups.
I&amp;rsquo;ve already attended my first meeting and I was blown away by how much work is done by the committee and the various sub-committees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leitrim Business Network</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/16/leitrim-business-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/16/leitrim-business-network/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really pleased to see how well the Leitrim Business Network is taking off. Johnny Beirne from Leitrim CEB and the team are really pushing it forward. I love seeing them evangelise the opportunities presented by online networking through tools like LinkedIn and of course the site itself is a group blog.
it@cork has shown how useful and influential a professional local business network can be, particularly one that understands technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Leader Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/05/itcork-leader-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2007 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/05/itcork-leader-awards/</guid>
      <description>This is such a great idea.
On November 1, 2007 it@cork will have their first ever Leader’s Awards. They want to recognise some of the leading companies and individuals in the community and have an evening of networking, reflection and celebration.
There are 4 categories:
 1. Emerging Company Award - to recognise a leading company in early stage business planning and execution 2. High Potential Award - to recognise a leading established company driving forward in international markets 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FireFox - A Web-browser, a Platform, a Framework</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/31/firefox-a-web-browser-a-platform-a-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2007 11:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/31/firefox-a-web-browser-a-platform-a-framework/</guid>
      <description>On August 8th, it@cork are hosting a talk by Marcio Galli. He is a Firefox Developer and will talk on Web development and advanced applications with upcoming Mozilla Firefox 3. Given some of the extremely cool things that are coming with FF3, this is a must-attend event if you are involved in web technologies.
Target audiences: Computer science students, web developers, software engineers, entrepreneurial individuals, and more.
Marcio Galli currently works as a consultant for the Mozilla project, with specific contribution to mobile projects such as the Mozilla Joey, Mozilla Minimo, and Mozilla development efforts in Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Job Seekers Link now live</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/15/motorola-job-seekers-link-now-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/15/motorola-job-seekers-link-now-live/</guid>
      <description>Deirdre Lacey from it@cork contacted me to tell me about a page they have put on their site:
The page allows staff from Motorola to post their details if they are job seeking. Prospective employers can follow up directly with candidates via email links. This system has worked very well is similar circumstances throughout the country.
it@Cork wish all Motorola employees well in their future plans.
This is a wonderful idea and I hope it works well for all involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee Club Announcement</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 21:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of discussion the inaugural Cork OpenCoffee Club will be held at 10am this Friday 16th in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s on Emmet Place in Cork City Centre. UseAMap.
The aim of the club is to bring together a good mix of entrepreneurs, investors, developers and marketers, plus anyone else who is interested in growing the start-up community in Cork. Organisations like it@cork and the CorkBIC are incredibly important in fostering professional networking in Cork and I hope we can make OpenCoffee complementary in many ways to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Q&amp;A and final comment</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-qa-and-final-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 18:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-qa-and-final-comment/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 5 out of 5
The Q&amp;amp;A; session didn&amp;rsquo;t last very long but did throw up some interesting points.
To kick off, there were various tech questions for Rob. Then Fergus was asked how long it took to launch Nooked, He replied that it was about a year after 3 different models. Walter was asked how he was hiring. He isn&amp;rsquo;t. There was a question about to get the right right developer expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Rob Burke</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-rob-burke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 16:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-rob-burke/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
As sponsers of the conference, it was only fair that Microsoft was given the opportunity to present their Web 2.0 wares. I talked to Rob the previous night to discover that he is an evangelist from Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Platform and Developer Group. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of this type of role within companies. Good evangelists can transform the image of a company and really re-invigorate employees as I believe Robert Scoble has done for Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
