<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>web2ireland on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/web2ireland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in web2ireland on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 09:52:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/web2ireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Want to speak at next Facebook Garage Ireland?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/05/19/want-to-speak-at-next-facebook-garage-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 09:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/05/19/want-to-speak-at-next-facebook-garage-ireland/</guid>
      <description>The first Facebook Garage Ireland was a massive success with 150+ people in attendance and a bunch of great talks and demos.
We&amp;rsquo;re planning the next one for June and have put the call out for speakers/demoers.
If you are doing anything with FB Apps or Connect and want to let people know, then grab the opportunity. Remember, we had RTE at the last one and made the news!
All details over on the Web2Ireland blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Web Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/13/le-web-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 10:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/13/le-web-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I attended Le Web on Tue/Wed this week in Paris. It is the leading web conference in Europe and this was my third year.
Despite a bunch of logistical problems, Loic and Geraldine Le Meur created yet another event that will stick in the mind for a long time. I was at the conference with multiple hats on:
  CEO of LouderVoice eager to meet potential partners and investors Guest Author for ReadWriteWeb looking at Le Web from technology perspective Co-Editor of Web2Ireland looking at Le Web from business perspective   My Web2Ireland post covers the general business mood and how it may affect Irish start-ups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web 2.0 Ireland - The story so far</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/12/22/web-20-ireland-the-story-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 15:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/12/22/web-20-ireland-the-story-so-far/</guid>
      <description>A little storm erupted this morning over the TechLudd initiative which was launched by some of those who went on the Paddy’s Valley trip to the USA. Paul Walsh from Segala considers it misguided and wonders why no attempt was made to reach out to existing networks in Ireland, particularly considering TechLudd is supposed to be about networking. I offered my few cents in support of Paul’s position and some decent debate ensued in the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web2Ireland Week in Dublin looks awesome</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2007 19:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</guid>
      <description>Look at the lineup (form Web2Ireland.org blog):
 Mashup University - Monday 10th/Tuesday 11th Mashup Camp - Wednesday 12th/Thursday 13th Paddy’s Valley Meet-up- Thursday 13th DemoBar and FOWA Road trip - Thursday 13th OpenCoffee - Friday 14th  The Mashup Camp and Uni really looks like a wonderful four days. Only €25 nominal sign-up to learn a ton of stuff. If you are a developer and you are not attending at least one day of this, you missing out on something special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Q&amp;A and final comment</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-qa-and-final-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 18:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-qa-and-final-comment/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 5 out of 5
The Q&amp;amp;A; session didn&amp;rsquo;t last very long but did throw up some interesting points.
To kick off, there were various tech questions for Rob. Then Fergus was asked how long it took to launch Nooked, He replied that it was about a year after 3 different models. Walter was asked how he was hiring. He isn&amp;rsquo;t. There was a question about to get the right right developer expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Rob Burke</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-rob-burke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 16:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-rob-burke/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
As sponsers of the conference, it was only fair that Microsoft was given the opportunity to present their Web 2.0 wares. I talked to Rob the previous night to discover that he is an evangelist from Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Platform and Developer Group. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of this type of role within companies. Good evangelists can transform the image of a company and really re-invigorate employees as I believe Robert Scoble has done for Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Walter Higgins</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-walter-higgins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 15:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-walter-higgins/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
For out and out geekful rapture, Walter&amp;rsquo;s presentation was a joy. I think it was a very necessary presentation to give (and provided a very nice counter-point to Rob&amp;rsquo;s which followed). There is a perception I think, particularly amongst a lot of the Web 2.0 tech press who appear to have no technical background, that creating a new Ajaxian WebApp is a weekends work mashing a few libraries and services together and alakazamm, it just works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Fergus Burns</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-fergus-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 13:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-fergus-burns/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
I met Fergus for the first time at the EI Web 2.0 Conference back in April but his reputation far preceded him. He has been described as the consummate networker but I think this does him an injustice - he is not just a genuine friendly guy, he is a doer. Whilst have the tech world talks about Web 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Review Intro</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-review-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 09:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-review-intro/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 5 out of 5
Tom, Catherine and all the team at IT@Cork put on a fantastic half day Web 2.0 conference on Thursday.
The geek dinner the night before set the scene perfectly - thanks again to Damien and all the organisers of that and Stormhoek for the wine. I finally got to meet Damien, Donncha, Gavin and a few others who I had previously only known through their blogs like Branedy and his lovely wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web 2.0 Conference Dublin - much food for thought</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/04/30/web-20-conference-dublin-much-food-for-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2006 09:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/04/30/web-20-conference-dublin-much-food-for-thought/</guid>
      <description>The Web 2.0 Conference in Dublin was a big success and was well worth attending. It was great to finally put faces to a lot of names in the Irish tech world and beyond. I went out the previous night to an informal meet-up arranged by Robert Smith. The layout of the place unfortunately was not conducive to talking to lots of the people who turned up which meant I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to talk to Marc Canter about Microformats and Structured Blogging until the following day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
