<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nooked on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/nooked/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nooked on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:54:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/nooked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nooked makes advertising personal</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/06/nooked-makes-advertising-personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 08:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/06/nooked-makes-advertising-personal/</guid>
      <description>The fundamental problem with advertising is that it has always taken the shotgun approach. Show the same ad to as many people as possible and hope some of them like it. Systems like Google AdSense have improved things a lot by showing ads related to the content on a web-page but they are still not ideal and give the person who owns the web-page minimal control beyond some simple competitor-exclusions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s about bloody time!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/14/its-about-bloody-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 12:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/14/its-about-bloody-time/</guid>
      <description>The Nooked blog is back in business and it&amp;rsquo;s with one zinger of a post. I cannot wait to see this stuff in the wild! RSS = Really Simple Shopping - best re-use of an acronym ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedburner not buying Nooked</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/14/feedburner-buying-nooked/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2006 19:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/14/feedburner-buying-nooked/</guid>
      <description>Well as ever it looks like Valleywag is about as accurate as the National Enquirer and I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be spreading their rubbish rumours. Fergus has stated that the story is untrue. It was just one of those stories that grows because it makes perfect sense even if it is not true.
Not that I&amp;rsquo;d ever believe a word on Valleywag but they are reporting that Feedburner has bought Nooked. If it&amp;rsquo;s true then huge congrats to Fergus and the team, it is much deserved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Fergus Burns</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-fergus-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 13:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-fergus-burns/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
I met Fergus for the first time at the EI Web 2.0 Conference back in April but his reputation far preceded him. He has been described as the consummate networker but I think this does him an injustice - he is not just a genuine friendly guy, he is a doer. Whilst have the tech world talks about Web 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
