<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris-Messina on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/chris-messina/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chris-Messina on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 15:21:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/chris-messina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Geek Dinners, BarCamps and Coworking</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/geek-dinners-barcamps-and-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/geek-dinners-barcamps-and-coworking/</guid>
      <description>I attended my first UK Geek Dinner last night after FoWA. Guests of honour were Tara Hunt and Chris Messina. I only chatted to Chris for a short while towards the end of the night and the bulk of the conversation was about BarCamp. I told him how important I thought BarCamps have been for the creation of a vibrant tech community in Ireland. I also wanted to thank him and Tantek and the others for starting something that I think is a true revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Start-up culture Panel at FoWA</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/21/european-start-up-culture-panel-at-fowa/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Carson - Carson Systems, Richard Moross - Moo, Mike Arrington - TechCrunch, Mike Butcher - Vecosys, Chris Messina - Citizen Agency, Saul Klein - Index Ventures, Max Jennings - eMomentum, Colin Donald - Futurescape, Tariq Krim - NetVibes. * Richard - Afraid of failure in Europe * Mike A - Stop talking and start doing, if we want to be like Silicon Valley. Smart people move to Silicon Valley which is a big help * Mike B - Subject is 18 months out of date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s all about YOU</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/26/its-all-about-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 08:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/26/its-all-about-you/</guid>
      <description>If you need one reason, just one, why microformats are important, then you need to read Chris&#39; latest post about the hResume Wordpress plugin over at FactoryCity. His comments are not just specific to hResume, they are relevant for all microformat marked-up PCEK. PCEK (aka Peck) being a horrendous acronym I came up with about 10 minutes ago after reading Tim Bray and it means &amp;ldquo;People Contributed Experience and Knowledge&amp;rdquo;. The critical part of Chris&#39; post is</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
