<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conferences on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/conferences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conferences on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 21:05:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/conferences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Talk at IWTC 2008</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/03/03/my-talk-at-iwtc-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 21:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/03/03/my-talk-at-iwtc-2008/</guid>
      <description>I spoke last week at the Irish Web Technologies Conference. My topic was &amp;ldquo;SMS, LBS and Social Networking&amp;rdquo; from the perspective of an enthusiastic punter and early adopter. I got a great response from the (albeit small) audience with particular interest shown in
 Buying music by SMS on downloadmusic.ie Live Video streaming from your phone on Qik Geo-tagging of photos and their map display on Flickr Vodafone offering a photo sharing site with 5MB in total available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events this week</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/26/events-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 09:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/26/events-this-week/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s an incredibly busy week of events in Dublin and Cork in the next few days. The ones that we&amp;rsquo;ll be attending are:
 xCellerate 2008 tomorrow - Half Day conference on raising funds and &amp;ldquo;bringing Silicon Valley to Ireland&amp;rdquo; IWTC - Irish Web Technology Conference. This starts tonight and runs until Friday. Conor is presenting on &amp;ldquo;SMS, LBS and Social Networks&amp;rdquo; on Thursday afternoon Irish Blog Awards on Saturday night - LouderVoice is sponsoring the Best Blog Post award BlogTalk 2008 - Blogging conference in Cork on Mon/Tue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Blogger Dinner</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/05/cork-blogger-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 19:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/05/cork-blogger-dinner/</guid>
      <description>Alexia Golez is arranging a Blogger Dinner in Cork for Sunday the 2nd March on the weekend of the Blogtalk Conference and WebCamp. You can expect some really interesting visitors (and locals!) to be there. Please let Alexia know if you wish to attend over on her blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking at IWTC 2008</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/04/speaking-at-iwtc-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 20:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/04/speaking-at-iwtc-2008/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m very pleased to have been invited to speak at the Irish Web Technology Conference on 28th February in Dublin. My 75 minute session is about SMS, Location Based Services and Social Networking. I&amp;rsquo;ll be very much doing this as an eager punter and coming from the web side rather than from the mobile industry. I hope that provides some new perspectives in this area. The summary is as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Web 3, Lundi au Mercredi</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/12/09/le-web-3-lundi-au-mercredi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/12/09/le-web-3-lundi-au-mercredi/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be presenting LouderVoice at Le Web 3 on Tuesday at 2.30pm. We&amp;rsquo;re up against 29 other web start-ups from around Europe and I have 7 minutes to dazzle. Wish us luck!
You can get me on my normal mobile (+353-87-9790297) or my MAXRoam numbers:
+353-1-5262888
+44-208-8199686
+1-206-420-5964</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS Seminar in Cork</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/10/15/gps-seminar-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 08:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/10/15/gps-seminar-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>I was sent information about a very meaty looking three day seminar organised by GPS Ireland in the NMCI facility of CIT in Ringaskiddy. It&amp;rsquo;s on from 22nd-24th October.
Day 1 is aboout Fundamentals of GPS/GNSS and is open to anyone interested in seeking conceptual and detailed explanations of GPS technology, operation, capabilities, applications and development trends.
Day 2 is a follow-on from the first day and is about GPS Fundamentals &amp;amp; Enhancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at TechCrunch40</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/12/loudervoice-at-techcrunch40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2007 12:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/12/loudervoice-at-techcrunch40/</guid>
      <description>Cross-posting from the LouderVoice Blog:
We are incredibly excited that an opportunity to attend TechCrunch40 in San Francisco next week has appeared. It is all due to the wonderful Pat Phelan of Cubic Telecom who offered a free ticket to a well deserving start-up. LouderVoice is that start-up and I&amp;rsquo;ll be there from Sunday until Wednesday afternoon.
If you are in the Bay area and would like to meet up and talk business and technology or you are from the investment community, I&amp;rsquo;d love to see you whilst I am there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you pass on DemoBar you can never complain again</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/if-you-pass-on-demobar-you-can-never-complain-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 18:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/if-you-pass-on-demobar-you-can-never-complain-again/</guid>
      <description>OK here&amp;rsquo;s the deal.
On Thursday September 13th, an event called DemoBar is being held. This is a chance for 10 web startups to demo their product to an audience consisting of their peers, the press, Irish investors, UK investors, Enterprise Ireland, the Future of WebApps conference organisers and a bunch of other people.
Not only that but we&amp;rsquo;ll be announcing shortly on the Web2Ireland.org site that EI is arranging for a pitch training session that afternoon for both Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley attendees and DemoBar participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web2Ireland Week in Dublin looks awesome</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2007 19:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/21/web2ireland-week-in-dublin-looks-awesome/</guid>
      <description>Look at the lineup (form Web2Ireland.org blog):
 Mashup University - Monday 10th/Tuesday 11th Mashup Camp - Wednesday 12th/Thursday 13th Paddy’s Valley Meet-up- Thursday 13th DemoBar and FOWA Road trip - Thursday 13th OpenCoffee - Friday 14th  The Mashup Camp and Uni really looks like a wonderful four days. Only €25 nominal sign-up to learn a ton of stuff. If you are a developer and you are not attending at least one day of this, you missing out on something special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like to present your webapp to 5000 people?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/10/like-to-present-your-webapp-to-5000-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2007 13:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/10/like-to-present-your-webapp-to-5000-people/</guid>
      <description>Web 2.0 Expo is coming to Berlin from 5th-8th November and it is a serious opportunity for those involved in web development in Ireland to get noticed.
Jennifer Pahlka, one of the organisers, is coming to Cork on July 14th and Tom Raftery has arranged an OpenDrinks Event that evening for any Irish people interested in going to the Web 2.0 Expo or, more importantly, for anyone hoping to present there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
