<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 23:07:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Have your start-up profiled by Ireland&#39;s number one ranked blogger</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 23:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</guid>
      <description>If you have a tech start-up and despair sometimes (as I do) over the lack of local press coverage of your efforts then help is at hand. Damien Mulley is offering to profile those who send him their company details. According to Technorati, he is the highest ranked blogger in Ireland and he also writes for the The Sunday Tribune so this can get you lots of interest.
Who knows, maybe certain startup-clueless newspapers (yes I&amp;rsquo;m talking about you Irish Examiner) might even pick up on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moffett Field here we come</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/12/moffett-field-here-we-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 11:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/12/moffett-field-here-we-come/</guid>
      <description>Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley has a definite date and now a hotel. And soon maybe even a t-shirt. We&amp;rsquo;ll set a closing date for signing up soon and spaces are limited so I encourage you to do so today!
If you know anyone in the Valley who you think would like to meet a bunch of Irish start-ups and techies, please contact them and let them know the details. If they bite, let us know too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee Club Announcement</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 21:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of discussion the inaugural Cork OpenCoffee Club will be held at 10am this Friday 16th in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s on Emmet Place in Cork City Centre. UseAMap.
The aim of the club is to bring together a good mix of entrepreneurs, investors, developers and marketers, plus anyone else who is interested in growing the start-up community in Cork. Organisations like it@cork and the CorkBIC are incredibly important in fostering professional networking in Cork and I hope we can make OpenCoffee complementary in many ways to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Ireland Mentor Panel</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/09/17/enterprise-ireland-mentor-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 10:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/09/17/enterprise-ireland-mentor-panel/</guid>
      <description>I recently did a presentation on our new business to an EI Mentor Panel. It was a very valuable exercise and I recommend that anyone in a start-up in Ireland do one as early as possible. Not only do you get excellent feedback from the panel but it is a great way of clarifying your own thoughts and tightening up your presentation skills.
The panel consisted of three people, one from a marketing background and two from a business background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Marketers are Snakes</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/08/22/all-marketers-are-snakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 19:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/08/22/all-marketers-are-snakes/</guid>
      <description>I bought Seth Godin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;All Marketers are Liars&amp;rdquo; last week and read it cover to cover in less than a week (a new record for me). It&amp;rsquo;s one of those books that just clicks with you instantly. You feel like a lot of what he is saying is obvious but taken as a whole, it tells a compelling story.
The timing of my reading was apt considering the sub-title is &amp;ldquo;The Power of Telling Authentic Stories in a Low-Trust World&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
