<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nokia on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/nokia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nokia on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 16:10:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/nokia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top Travel Tip</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/08/31/top-travel-tip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 16:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/08/31/top-travel-tip/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned before that a few months back I was in London for an event and I decided to forego my laptop and just bring my Nokia N95-8GB. This would provide e-mail, RSS reading and Twitter. Of course I was petrified of the roaming data charges that can happen abroad and made sure to just use Wifi where possible. Unfortunately my hotel room had a very poor wifi signal so I decided to bite the bullet and check my email using the (much maligned by me) Vodafone Live APN on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Nokia wake up like they did with paper products?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/will-nokia-wake-up-like-they-did-with-paper-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 13:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/will-nokia-wake-up-like-they-did-with-paper-products/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking recently about Nokia and my general feeling is that they are missing many simple opportunities to retain leadership in mobile development.
Apart from one crappy Panasonic and a dog-slow Sony-Ericcson T610, I&amp;rsquo;ve always used Nokia phones. They have been solid workhorses with just the right combination of features for me. Until last year, that meant Series 40 phones but I then finally succumbed and bought an N70 a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Nokia</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/13/bloody-nokia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 14:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/13/bloody-nokia/</guid>
      <description>I paid a fair chunk of cash for an N70 last year in the expectation that it would be the solution to all my mobile app needs for the foreseeable future and replace things like the Tungsten T. Overall it&amp;rsquo;s a fine but slow phone and there are some nice applications for it (Opera mini being particularly good). But one thing that is annoying the hell out of me is that every new announcement from Nokia seems to only be about Series 60 version 3 phones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
