<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Administration on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/administration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Administration on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 11:05:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/administration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Looking for an experienced web developer</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/19/looking-for-an-experienced-web-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 11:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/19/looking-for-an-experienced-web-developer/</guid>
      <description>Lead Web Developer Required  Listed: Jan 19 2007 10:30:00 UTC
Expires: Apr 30 2007 10:30:00 UTC
We are currently using a full outsource model for both the development and design of LouderVoice. We are aiming to change this to a hybrid inhouse/outsource approach as we get closer to full launch.
To that end we are looking to hire a full-time experienced web developer. If you have a strong background in end-to-end web development and you are looking for all the opportunities that being the lead developer in a start-up provides then we want to hear from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comments from April to September back online and sxore remover now available here</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/10/31/comments-from-april-to-september-back-online-and-sxore-remover-now-available-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 10:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/10/31/comments-from-april-to-september-back-online-and-sxore-remover-now-available-here/</guid>
      <description>As regular readers know, I used the sxore comment system on this blog from April to September. Whilst the intent of sxore was good, the reality fell far short. It was a big mistake handing over my comment data to a third party where that data was not transparently available to me if I ever wished to stop using their services.
I finally bit the bullet a few weeks ago and turned off sxore due to the serious bugs and lack of development on the important features of the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mail Glitch</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/09/03/mail-glitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2006 18:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/09/03/mail-glitch/</guid>
      <description>Small mail glitch over the past 24 hours. If you sent anything from early Saturday morning to early Sunday evening to any Argolon address, I&amp;rsquo;m afraid it got devnulled. Please re-send.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BT Ireland- the good and the bad</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/08/12/bt-ireland-the-good-and-the-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 14:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/08/12/bt-ireland-the-good-and-the-bad/</guid>
      <description>We decided to switch over to BT Ireland/EsatBT recently to try to minimise costs during the startup of the new venture. I know they are infamous for their incompetent billing but the value really is very good - The Total Talk + 3Mbs Broadband package blows Eircom out of the water.
But it looks like the billing department are not the only ones who need some training in BT. You cannot sign-up to their service online using either Firefox or IE7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Web Developer required</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/15/key-web-developer-required/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 09:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/15/key-web-developer-required/</guid>
      <description>Key Developer Required  Listed: Jul 15 2006 10:30:00 BST
Expires: Oct 31 2006 10:30:00 UTC
Argolon has started development on a new user-centric web application which will launch in Q1 2007. We are looking for a skilled and ambitious web-developer to lead the creation of our site. The ideal candidate will come from an application development background but with a strong understanding of Web UI design and a commitment to XHTML and CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first of many changes</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/03/15/the-first-of-many-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2006 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/03/15/the-first-of-many-changes/</guid>
      <description>This blog has been very quiet of late due to some major activity in the background. Yesterdays look n feel change to the site was just the starting point. I&amp;rsquo;ll post more details over the coming days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeking Oracle and SQL Server Developers</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/09/26/seeking-oracle-and-sql-server-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2005 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/09/26/seeking-oracle-and-sql-server-developers/</guid>
      <description>Due to the continued growth of the company, we are currently looking for experienced Oracle PL-SQL or SQL Server T-SQL Developers. Knowledge of Reporting and BI tools would be considered a major advantage as would a background in Enterprise Java development. Ideal candidates will have between 4 and 7 years experience. We are interested in talking to those seeking both permanent and contract positions. If you think you fit the bill and you are interested in working with us to deliver into the world leaders in enterprise technologies, please forward you CV to hr@argolon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Launch</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/06/20/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2005 21:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/06/20/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Today we launched the new the Argolon Solutions web-site built around a Wordpress Blog. We intend to make this site blog-driven so that all news relevant to our target markets can be aggregated and discussed. All feedback is welcome. Please take advantage of the RSS links below to stay up-to-date with all of our news and views.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
