<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BarCamp on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/barcamp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BarCamp on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 15:44:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/barcamp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork III Next Weekend</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/11/07/barcamp-cork-iii-next-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 15:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/11/07/barcamp-cork-iii-next-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As co-organiser of the first two Cork BarCamps, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to see the third one is happening next Saturday 14th Nov in the fabulous Cork International Airport Hotel. The able organisers this time around are Gordon Murray, Ciara Crossan and Ciara Feely.
BarCamp is one of those free conferences where you leave having gained far more from the day than you expect. It&amp;rsquo;s the serendipity that makes it special. I have built many friendships and business relationships with the people I meet there over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork II on November 1st</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/30/barcamp-cork-ii-on-november-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 08:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/30/barcamp-cork-ii-on-november-1st/</guid>
      <description>It has been over two years since the last one, but BarCamp is finally coming back to Cork. It&amp;rsquo;s soon, very soon, only four weeks away. The venue is the lovely Webworks building in the City Centre, just like the last time.
We have a strong vision for this event and we need your help to make it happen on the day. Please read the first set of posts and give us your feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Galway Open Coffee Announced!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/12/first-galway-open-coffee-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 11:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/12/first-galway-open-coffee-announced/</guid>
      <description>Aidan Finn just announced Galway OCC on Twitter. Upcoming.org page here. I&amp;rsquo;d been hoping for this one, I think it&amp;rsquo;ll be a big success. Looking forward to the reports. That plus BarCamp Galway are two great excuses for us to head up there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCampDublin Today</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/21/barcampdublin-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2007 07:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/21/barcampdublin-today/</guid>
      <description>Hope you all have an amazing day and shake things up a bit!
Sorry I can&amp;rsquo;t make it this time. Next time I promise.
If you are in Dublin today, head on over to the Digital Hub to see the future of conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content and Convergence</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/17/content-and-convergence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 19:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/17/content-and-convergence/</guid>
      <description>Haydn has offered up some quite controversial opinions on where many Irish web companies should put their energies and also what the BarCampDublin focus should be. It&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;d like to see argued from both points of view so please head over to Mediangler and offer your thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Dublin coming on April 21st</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/12/barcamp-dublin-coming-on-april-21st/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 14:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/12/barcamp-dublin-coming-on-april-21st/</guid>
      <description>Elly and the gang have been hard at work putting together BarCamp Dublin and it looks like a winner. This is the third one after Cork and Waterford and I love the look of the speaker line-up. If you are free at all on Saturday week I&amp;rsquo;d encourage you to head over. Do sign-up so they know how many people to expect.
Some of the talks that catch my eye include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geek Dinners, BarCamps and Coworking</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/geek-dinners-barcamps-and-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/geek-dinners-barcamps-and-coworking/</guid>
      <description>I attended my first UK Geek Dinner last night after FoWA. Guests of honour were Tara Hunt and Chris Messina. I only chatted to Chris for a short while towards the end of the night and the bulk of the conversation was about BarCamp. I told him how important I thought BarCamps have been for the creation of a vibrant tech community in Ireland. I also wanted to thank him and Tantek and the others for starting something that I think is a true revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from BarCampIreland SouthEast starting to appear</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</guid>
      <description>Keith has uploaded videos of the &amp;ldquo;Finding money for your start-up&amp;rdquo; session. I enjoyed the differing views of the panel on this topic but anyone who thought they&amp;rsquo;d come away with &amp;ldquo;so that&amp;rsquo;s how I do it&amp;rdquo; would have been disappointed. There should definitely be a follow-up session at BarCamp Dublin with a focus on successful early-stage tech startup fund-raising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Ireland</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/24/barcamp-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/24/barcamp-ireland/</guid>
      <description>Fergus, Paul and James have all blogged about BarCamp Ireland already. I just bit the bullet and signed up to talk rather than just attend. I&amp;rsquo;ve a few things I can usefully contribute:
 My experiences so far with raising funding and dealing with state bodies (and 2002 vs 2006) Progress on outsourcing by the time BarCamp comes around (and purchaser vs vendor view) Microformats from a business perspective (no, I will not argue about XML)  [tags]Barcamp, Barcamp Ireland[/tags]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
