<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jobs on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jobs on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 17:55:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New BES limits OKed by EU!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just heard (via Joe Drumgoole&amp;rsquo;s blog) that the new BES limits annnounced last November have finally been approved by the EU. This is fantastic news.
This is the official EU newsletter announcement:
Notification or Registration Date:	23.05.2007 DG Responsible:	Competition DG Related Procedures:	N 311 / 2004
Decision on 23.08.2007:	Article 4ยง3 - decision not to raise objections
This presumably means that Enterprise Ireland should be processing new company certs starting five days ago and the Revenue Commissioners should be approving RICTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Person required to do some short-term CSS&#43;XHTML work</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/20/person-required-to-do-some-short-term-cssxhtml-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 12:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/20/person-required-to-do-some-short-term-cssxhtml-work/</guid>
      <description>As LouderVoice races towards full launch, we have a requirement for someone to do CSS and XHTML work for us between now and then. Basically this person will have to take our existing design, apply it to any new features and pages on the site and tweak what is there already.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t a huge amount of work (time-scale is over the next few weeks and effort is probably less than a person-week), does not require design expertise and would suit anyone between major contracts or looking for a nice side project to exercise their mark-up muscles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee off to a flying start</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 17:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</guid>
      <description>Wow that was some morning in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s! I&amp;rsquo;d never been there before and the venue was just perfect. I arrived in to find a few of the guys along with Don the owner who stayed for the entire session. A huge thanks to Don for covering the cost of the refreshments today and for getting Wifi installed with almost no notice.
We had 20+ people turn up with the exact mix I was hoping for:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Job Seekers Link now live</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/15/motorola-job-seekers-link-now-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/15/motorola-job-seekers-link-now-live/</guid>
      <description>Deirdre Lacey from it@cork contacted me to tell me about a page they have put on their site:
The page allows staff from Motorola to post their details if they are job seeking. Prospective employers can follow up directly with candidates via email links. This system has worked very well is similar circumstances throughout the country.
it@Cork wish all Motorola employees well in their future plans.
This is a wonderful idea and I hope it works well for all involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for an experienced web developer</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/01/19/looking-for-an-experienced-web-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 11:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/01/19/looking-for-an-experienced-web-developer/</guid>
      <description>Lead Web Developer Required  Listed: Jan 19 2007 10:30:00 UTC
Expires: Apr 30 2007 10:30:00 UTC
We are currently using a full outsource model for both the development and design of LouderVoice. We are aiming to change this to a hybrid inhouse/outsource approach as we get closer to full launch.
To that end we are looking to hire a full-time experienced web developer. If you have a strong background in end-to-end web development and you are looking for all the opportunities that being the lead developer in a start-up provides then we want to hear from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICT Champions Scheme</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/08/20/ict-champions-scheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2006 11:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/08/20/ict-champions-scheme/</guid>
      <description>Back in June I took part in a workshop in preparation for taking part in the ICT Champions scheme. This is a joint effort by many organisations involved in electronics, science and computing in Ireland to get schoolkids interested in these areas. The idea is to visit local schools, tell them what you do and what your career has been and show them (via things like iPods) how engineering and technology are part of every aspect of their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendations for Web Application Development shops?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2006 11:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/20/recommendations-for-web-application-development-shops/</guid>
      <description>We intend to outsource the bulk of the development of our application. This will be broken down into several areas including:
 Design XHTML/CSS Application development Hosting Operations  I have received plenty of recommendations for Design and some for XHTML/CSS but other than Ryan Carson recommending Nick in Plum Digital Media (and more on yesterday&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;How to build a WebApp&amp;rdquo; workshop later), it is proving difficult to get recommendations for top-class web application development houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Web Developer required</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/15/key-web-developer-required/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 09:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/15/key-web-developer-required/</guid>
      <description>Key Developer Required  Listed: Jul 15 2006 10:30:00 BST
Expires: Oct 31 2006 10:30:00 UTC
Argolon has started development on a new user-centric web application which will launch in Q1 2007. We are looking for a skilled and ambitious web-developer to lead the creation of our site. The ideal candidate will come from an application development background but with a strong understanding of Web UI design and a commitment to XHTML and CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
