<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 19:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So Twitter is just for mindless prattle eh?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/10/29/so-twitter-is-just-for-mindless-prattle-eh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 19:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/10/29/so-twitter-is-just-for-mindless-prattle-eh/</guid>
      <description>Every so often, Twitter surprises me. When you think you&amp;rsquo;ve had enough of the consultants, snake oil salesmen, link baiters and spammers, someone uses it to blow your socks off with great customer service. Drugstore.com just did that for me.
I make maybe two large orders a year from drugstore.com which is based in the US (and owned by Amazon I think). The main purchase is a generic OTC medicine which costs a ridiculous fortune in Ireland in branded form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, 1000 times, yes.</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/09/20/yes-1000-times-yes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 11:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/09/20/yes-1000-times-yes/</guid>
      <description>Read Pat Phelan&amp;rsquo;s post on &amp;ldquo;Irish Silicon Valley&amp;rdquo; now, right now.
I don&amp;rsquo;t need to add anything except, please listen to the man, he knows what he is talking about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes from Conor in today&#39;s Sunday Business Post</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/06/14/quotes-from-conor-in-todays-sunday-business-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/06/14/quotes-from-conor-in-todays-sunday-business-post/</guid>
      <description>The SBP has an excellent supplement about Cork in today&amp;rsquo;s edition. Hopefully it&amp;rsquo;ll make it onto their web-site at some stage. Caroline Allen dedicated the entire back page to start-ups and include quotes from CorkBIC, Rubicon Centre, it@cork and Argolon/LouderVoice. The full piece is well worth a read, particularly considering the same message was coming loud and clear from us all. Hopefully someone in Government will read it and get that message!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piece in Business &amp; Finance Magazine</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/02/03/piece-in-business-finance-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 13:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/02/03/piece-in-business-finance-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Adam Maguire kindly invited several of us to give our top IT money-saving tips for 2009 in a recent issue of Business &amp;amp; Finance. That piece is now up on his blog. I naturally focused on Cloud Computing and SaaS. Thanks Adam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyvästi Jaiku</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/01/15/hyvasti-jaiku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 10:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/01/15/hyvasti-jaiku/</guid>
      <description>From ReadWriteWeb, Jaiku is to be shutdown.
I know a lot of webapp businesses are bought by Google and die through lack of attention. In our innocence, many of us thought Jaiku would be different. We thought there was a masterplan. We thought Jaiku would be the heart of the Android Address Book. The ultimate mobile social network with millions of users instantly.
We were completely and utterly wrong. Jaiku was bought to get some amazing minds, like Jyri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our 2009 Predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</guid>
      <description>The 2008 predictions weren&amp;rsquo;t the most accurate. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how we do for 2009.
 The Android platform will be absolutely huge. With Motorola, Sony Ericsson and a raft of Tier 2 manufacturers signed up, it will become _the _mobile platform from the mid to high end. Ignore the HTC G1, that&amp;rsquo;s just a rough first attempt by one manufacturer.  Despite Android, iPhone will remain big. There is always that 10% of the market who like paying extra for &amp;ldquo;luxury&amp;rdquo; brands SaaS ecommerce providers will go mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A look back to last year&#39;s predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/a-look-back-to-last-years-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/a-look-back-to-last-years-predictions/</guid>
      <description>My predictions for 2008 were very hit and miss (mainly miss), here&amp;rsquo;s a quick re-cap:
  Cubic Telecom will have a £100m exit
 * Not yet. 2008 was an amazing year for Pat and the team with deals happening at breakneck pace.    European Founders, Howzat Media, TAG or Advent will do a deal with a web or mobile start-up here
 * Again not yet. I still think this will happen    More foreign VCs will invest in Irish web start-ups than Irish VCs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Respect</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/07/respect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 08:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/07/respect/</guid>
      <description>My business hero is my Dad. He left a secure job in Dublin to join a startup in Kilkenny in the early 1970&amp;rsquo;s. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t a tech startup, it was a dairy one, called Avonmore-Avongate. That team built a global business over the next few decades.
My most recent business hero is Pat Phelan. He overcame huge personal crisis to firstly build a great business locally and then build MaxRoam. What he has achieved with MaxRoam in those timescales is close to miraculous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Cork Enterprise Board Support</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/07/24/west-cork-enterprise-board-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 08:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/07/24/west-cork-enterprise-board-support/</guid>
      <description>I spent a very interesting afternoon talking to Christine O&amp;rsquo;Donovan in WCEB in Clonakilty on Tuesday. We covered a pretty wide range of topics and I was highly impressed by the range of services they offer local businesses.

Our big area of mutual frustration was the lack of take-up on the Tech-Check scheme. I&amp;rsquo;ve written about it before on my personal blog and in summary, if you are a local biz in Ireland with even one laptop and you&amp;rsquo;ve never even talked to an Enterprise Board, then you are missing out hugely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish SMEs and Apple Macs</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/06/03/irish-smes-and-apple-macs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/06/03/irish-smes-and-apple-macs/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just been talking to a small local business that uses Apple Macs exclusively for all their computing needs. The owners expressed frustration over the lack of support they receive from state agencies in areas like training etc. In fact, they said that grants were offered at one stage to help small biz buy PCs but Macs were excluded!
These people almost felt like they were the only small biz using Macs in all of Cork.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
