<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>irish on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/irish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in irish on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/irish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our 2009 Predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</guid>
      <description>The 2008 predictions weren&amp;rsquo;t the most accurate. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how we do for 2009.
 The Android platform will be absolutely huge. With Motorola, Sony Ericsson and a raft of Tier 2 manufacturers signed up, it will become _the _mobile platform from the mid to high end. Ignore the HTC G1, that&amp;rsquo;s just a rough first attempt by one manufacturer.  Despite Android, iPhone will remain big. There is always that 10% of the market who like paying extra for &amp;ldquo;luxury&amp;rdquo; brands SaaS ecommerce providers will go mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have your start-up profiled by Ireland&#39;s number one ranked blogger</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 23:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</guid>
      <description>If you have a tech start-up and despair sometimes (as I do) over the lack of local press coverage of your efforts then help is at hand. Damien Mulley is offering to profile those who send him their company details. According to Technorati, he is the highest ranked blogger in Ireland and he also writes for the The Sunday Tribune so this can get you lots of interest.
Who knows, maybe certain startup-clueless newspapers (yes I&amp;rsquo;m talking about you Irish Examiner) might even pick up on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Web Apps on Startup 2.0 Directory</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/15/irish-web-apps-on-startup-20-directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 19:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/15/irish-web-apps-on-startup-20-directory/</guid>
      <description>The Startup 2.0 guys have launched a wiki to try and build a Europe-wide directory of web applications. Make sure to add your app. The Irish page is here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A great addition to UseAMap</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/14/a-great-addition-to-useamap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 09:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/14/a-great-addition-to-useamap/</guid>
      <description>Vinny Glennon has a genuinely useful site in UseAMap. Starting from the simple idea of doing a &amp;ldquo;TinyURL for Maps&amp;rdquo;, Vinny has built one of my favourite mapping apps.
The most recent addition is a huge boon to those of us who live in The Google Maps Darklands - UseAMap is now integrated with Yahoo Maps too.
Both Yahoo and Microsoft do a far superior job of mapping West Cork than Google.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
