<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 17:44:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Nokia Ovi Store a Rip-Off?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/05/25/new-nokia-ovi-store-a-rip-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 17:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/05/25/new-nokia-ovi-store-a-rip-off/</guid>
      <description>The new Nokia Ovi Store is in the process of going live around the world with Ireland, for a change, being one of the first to get it.
This is their response to the iPhone App Store and Android Market. You install it by opening the Download! App on your phone (for N-series anyway). Takes ages to install and phone must be rebooted.
My initial feeling is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel wildly different to that Download!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of HTC G1 Mobile Phone (Google Android)</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/review-of-htc-g1-mobile-phone-google-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 10:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/review-of-htc-g1-mobile-phone-google-android/</guid>
      <description>This first generation Google Android phone is an interesting mish-mash of brilliant software and so-so hardware. The touch screen is fantastic and the UI is almost perfect. Whilst it can&amp;rsquo;t compete with the N95-8GB on multimedia capabilities, for our business it kicks its ass.
The G1 is not available in Ireland and may never be. So far it has been released in the USA and the UK. Calls to CPW in Enniskillen drew a blank as they had no idea what I was talking about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia Maps 2.0 broken in Ireland?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/10/26/nokia-maps-20-broken-in-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 12:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/10/26/nokia-maps-20-broken-in-ireland/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been raving about Nokia Maps since I got my N95-8GB last December. Having voice-guided turn-by-turn directions on your phone is a killer app. It totally saved us getting back from Carnac to Roscoff this summer after printed Google Maps made a total mess of the outbound journey.
However something has gone badly wrong in Ireland and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how long the problem has been there. I&amp;rsquo;m running the latest V30 firmware on my N95-8GB which includes the latest Nokia Maps 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PutPlace is backup for the rest of us</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/07/01/putplace-is-backup-for-the-rest-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 20:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/07/01/putplace-is-backup-for-the-rest-of-us/</guid>
      <description>PutPlace may finally be the consumer-friendly application that gets the average punter securing their data and accessing it from wherever they like. A solid set of features with an easy-to-use site shows Microsoft et al how this should be done.

I&amp;rsquo;ve been talking to Joe Drumgoole about PutPlace for as long as I&amp;rsquo;ve known him. To be honest, I never quite grasped what it was about when I heard phrases like Digital Lifestyle Aggregator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N810 leaves me cold</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/06/22/n810-leaves-me-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 10:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/06/22/n810-leaves-me-cold/</guid>
      <description>I really thought I would love this device considering how much I like its old N770 brother. However it completely misses the mark and I can find no place for it in my daily workflow. Dare I say it, I would prefer an iPod Touch!
Last May at Cork OpenCoffee, Gordon Murray told everyone about an amazing bargain on Expansys. Nokia N770 Internet Tablets were selling for approx €100. By the end of the coffee morning, more than 10 had been ordered and after a few hours humming and hawing I got one too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outcome of testing Mobile Broadband (O2 and Vodafone)</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/06/10/outcome-of-testing-mobile-broadband-o2-and-vodafone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 15:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/06/10/outcome-of-testing-mobile-broadband-o2-and-vodafone/</guid>
      <description>This is actually a combined review of O2 and Vodafone Ireland mobile broadband services since I tested them in parallel. Neither is a replacement for fixed-line BB but in certain situations, the O2 modem is extremely fast and was my winner overall.
I&amp;rsquo;ve railed against both O2 and Voda on repeated occasions for not offering decent value proper data plans on phones. I&amp;rsquo;ve also read a wide variety of opinions on the various mobile broadband offferings with Three getting the most abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Nokia N95-8GB</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/03/16/review-of-nokia-n95-8gb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 21:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/03/16/review-of-nokia-n95-8gb/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for the ultimate business phone rather than the gadget equivalent of a Prada handbag, then this is the device for you. Quite simply the best phone I&amp;rsquo;ve ever owned.
Cards on the table - I love this phone. I&amp;rsquo;d marry it if it was legal. The rest of this review is an ode to &amp;ldquo;what computers have become&amp;rdquo;.
I&amp;rsquo;ve generally owned middle-of-the-road good business phones, all Nokia, with two short lived diversions to Panasonic and Sony-Ericcson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two weeks on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/27/two-weeks-on-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 16:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/27/two-weeks-on-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Due to major problems with one of our desktops, I donated my main XP desktop to the COO and I decided to use the Ubuntu file server as my desktop for a week &amp;ldquo;just to see&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m no Linux newbie, having started with Slackware in 1996 and gone through every iteration of RedHat and Fedora Core since. A few diversions to Suse and Mandriva were failures.
My Linux usage has mainly been server focused but I&amp;rsquo;ve often used the desktops either remotely using XWin on Cygwin or in a VMWare virtual machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaiku</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/06/jaiku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2007 19:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/06/jaiku/</guid>
      <description>Jaiku
This Finnish competitor to Twitter is a fantastic micro-blogging and life-streaming site. Every time Twitter goes down they gain more users. But is it enough?
I&amp;rsquo;ve been one of the most active users of the Twitter micro-blogging website in the country for quite a while. However I have also been a vocal critic. It&amp;rsquo;s brilliant simplicity in doing one thing well is being damaged by its inability to do that one thing well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
