<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>business-expansion-scheme on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/business-expansion-scheme/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business-expansion-scheme on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 15:08:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/business-expansion-scheme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice BES 2009 (Business Expansion Scheme)</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/11/15/loudervoice-bes-2009-business-expansion-scheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 15:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/11/15/loudervoice-bes-2009-business-expansion-scheme/</guid>
      <description>The LouderVoice customer reviews system for business has moved into high-gear in 2009. Clients are deploying our EasyReview widget on their e-commerce sites every week. Our first US customer will go live this month along with many more Irish sites. Our second UK site will go live early in the new year.
The most recent research by Internet Retailer tells you everything you need to know about how important reviews are to businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon Solutions &amp; LouderVoice BES 2008</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 11:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</guid>
      <description>We have just kicked off our BES 2008 offering which is built around the LouderVoice business. If you are interested in hearing more about this investment opportunity or discussing direct equity investments, please contact Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill on conor AT loudervoice DOT com or +353-87-9790297.
Over the past few months we have been trialling our business services with several clients. Some of those are already live, others will go live over the next quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A word of thanks</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 14:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</guid>
      <description>Founders of start-ups tend to spend a lot of time griping about things. I could write an essay on how it took from Aug 28th to Dec 3rd for Enterprise Ireland to issue a document needed to get us BES approval. Instead I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the positive part of that story.
On Dec 3rd, EI shuffled the paperwork-exercise out the door and it arrived in the Revenue Commissioners. Our solicitors also submitted our RICT outline application around the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon BES Scheme</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/argolon-bes-scheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 19:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/argolon-bes-scheme/</guid>
      <description>We will be announcing our BES scheme as soon as the initial paperwork has been processed.
If you want to hear more about any of the investment opportunities in Argolon Solutions and the LouderVoice web-site please contact me via any of the methods listed here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
