<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/investment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 15:21:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/investment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising Discussion on The Last Word</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, I was on TodayFM&amp;rsquo;s The Last Word radio show with Professor Frank Roche talking to Matt Cooper. The topic was centered on fund raising in the current economic climate. You can hear what we had to say in this audio clip. The interview starts about 4 minutes 30 seconds in.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that our 2008 BES offering is open until Dec 31st. The response to-date has been very positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon Solutions &amp; LouderVoice BES 2008</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 11:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</guid>
      <description>We have just kicked off our BES 2008 offering which is built around the LouderVoice business. If you are interested in hearing more about this investment opportunity or discussing direct equity investments, please contact Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill on conor AT loudervoice DOT com or +353-87-9790297.
Over the past few months we have been trialling our business services with several clients. Some of those are already live, others will go live over the next quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon BES Update</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/12/08/argolon-bes-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 16:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/12/08/argolon-bes-update/</guid>
      <description>Argolon Solutions expects to receive RICT Outline approval shortly for its proposed Business Expansion Scheme. Tax Relief for 2007 under the new limits should be possible.
If you are interested in receiving an information memorandum which describes the details of our scheme, please contact me on conor AT argolon DOT com or +353-87-9790297
[tags]BES, Business Expansion Scheme, Investment, Finance, Tax Relief, RICT[/tags]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pitch Videos from Irish Start-Ups In Palo Alto</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/12/06/pitch-videos-from-irish-start-ups-in-palo-alto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 11:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/12/06/pitch-videos-from-irish-start-ups-in-palo-alto/</guid>
      <description>The Enterprise Ireland and InterTradeIreland VC Forum pitching event in Silicon Valley on Tuesday looks to have been a great event. Five Irish web start-ups pitched to a panel of local VCs and an invited audience. You can see all the videos over at the Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley blog. The really interesting part for me was the questions from the VCs. They have a very strong focus on competitive advantage. It&amp;rsquo;s well worth your time watching all five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BES/SCS Briefing in Clarion on Monday</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-briefing-in-clarion-on-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 10:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-briefing-in-clarion-on-monday/</guid>
      <description>CorkBIC have arranged a briefing session on BES/SCS next Monday too. Whilst the Rubicon session is specifically targetted at start-ups, this one is more for the wider business community.
Short presentations will be made by:
Kevin Kenny, Tax Partner, Ernst &amp;amp; Young Clare Creamer, Assistant Principal, Revenue Commissioners Gerry O’Brien, Enterprise Ireland
Monday 12th November at 4pm – 5.15pm (to be followed by drinks reception) in the Clarion Hotel, Cork</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoiltchild looking for advice</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/10/29/spoiltchild-looking-for-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 22:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/10/29/spoiltchild-looking-for-advice/</guid>
      <description>Good post from Alan of Spoiltchild wondering about their investment strategy for Toddle and future apps. If you have any knowledge in this area, why not head over and leave a comment?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at TechCrunch40</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/12/loudervoice-at-techcrunch40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2007 12:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/12/loudervoice-at-techcrunch40/</guid>
      <description>Cross-posting from the LouderVoice Blog:
We are incredibly excited that an opportunity to attend TechCrunch40 in San Francisco next week has appeared. It is all due to the wonderful Pat Phelan of Cubic Telecom who offered a free ticket to a well deserving start-up. LouderVoice is that start-up and I&amp;rsquo;ll be there from Sunday until Wednesday afternoon.
If you are in the Bay area and would like to meet up and talk business and technology or you are from the investment community, I&amp;rsquo;d love to see you whilst I am there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon BES Scheme</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/argolon-bes-scheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 19:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/argolon-bes-scheme/</guid>
      <description>We will be announcing our BES scheme as soon as the initial paperwork has been processed.
If you want to hear more about any of the investment opportunities in Argolon Solutions and the LouderVoice web-site please contact me via any of the methods listed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you pass on DemoBar you can never complain again</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/if-you-pass-on-demobar-you-can-never-complain-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 18:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/if-you-pass-on-demobar-you-can-never-complain-again/</guid>
      <description>OK here&amp;rsquo;s the deal.
On Thursday September 13th, an event called DemoBar is being held. This is a chance for 10 web startups to demo their product to an audience consisting of their peers, the press, Irish investors, UK investors, Enterprise Ireland, the Future of WebApps conference organisers and a bunch of other people.
Not only that but we&amp;rsquo;ll be announcing shortly on the Web2Ireland.org site that EI is arranging for a pitch training session that afternoon for both Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley attendees and DemoBar participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New BES limits OKed by EU!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just heard (via Joe Drumgoole&amp;rsquo;s blog) that the new BES limits annnounced last November have finally been approved by the EU. This is fantastic news.
This is the official EU newsletter announcement:
Notification or Registration Date:	23.05.2007 DG Responsible:	Competition DG Related Procedures:	N 311 / 2004
Decision on 23.08.2007:	Article 4§3 - decision not to raise objections
This presumably means that Enterprise Ireland should be processing new company certs starting five days ago and the Revenue Commissioners should be approving RICTs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
