<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blogging on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/blogging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blogging on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 20:17:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/blogging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chronicle the development of an app and a business?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/29/chronicle-the-development-of-an-app-and-a-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 20:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/29/chronicle-the-development-of-an-app-and-a-business/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Murray of eWrite was asking on Twitter this evening what people thought of the idea of him documenting publicly the development of his new product and the business around it. In other words, blogging about it, warts and all.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a superb idea and could be of great benefit both to his business and to others who read it. If he can build a good readership then it could become a focal point for people to discuss lots of the standard issues around building a technology business in Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Any precedents on Libel and Defamation Law for Bloggers in Ireland?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/18/any-precedents-on-libel-and-defamation-law-for-bloggers-in-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 14:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/18/any-precedents-on-libel-and-defamation-law-for-bloggers-in-ireland/</guid>
      <description>Mike Butcher has just published a very useful piece on how to protect yourself as a blogger if you write something that results in a libel action being mounted against you and your content. It is all based around &amp;ldquo;The Reynolds defense of Responsible Journalism&amp;rdquo;. Whilst it makes total sense to me as a lay-person, it clearly is only directly relevant to UK bloggers.
Since it&amp;rsquo;s generally felt that Irish libel law is even more ridiculous than that of the UK, I wonder if there are any similar cases/precedents that apply here?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weathering a blogstorm</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/18/weathering-a-blogstorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 12:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/18/weathering-a-blogstorm/</guid>
      <description>One aspect of blogging (particularly business blogging) that worries some people is when something negative is written about them. This can sometimes erupt into a blogstorm with a huge hullabaloo across multiple blogs. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a few over the past few years and each company/person handled it differently.
Frank Prendergast has written a very thoughtful post on this topic and I&amp;rsquo;ll be recommending it to all new (and old!) bloggers. The essence of his advice is to keep a level head, state your case, apologise if you are in the wrong and move on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new Cork Business Blog</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/14/a-new-cork-business-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 16:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/14/a-new-cork-business-blog/</guid>
      <description>Just spotted that the YouGetItBack guys in Cork nowhave a blog. It&amp;rsquo;s all about the business of Lost and Found and whilst they only started on Monday, the posts are flying in.
I wrote about them on my personal blog wayyy back in June 2006 when I found out about their initial product/service. It was a great idea then and it still is now. Buy a sticker for your phone/iPod etc, register the sticker code, put sticker on item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Launches</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 13:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday we quietly unveiled LouderVoice. If you want a reviews site which takes a fundamentally different approach to everyone else then you&amp;rsquo;ll like what we have built.
Bloggers who write reviews now have a site which is built around enabling them to publish reviews to blogs in a widely accepted format. Everyone else now has a site where they can find great reviews, read them on those blogs and then rate them, share them and subscribe to more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
