<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BES on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/bes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BES on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 15:08:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/bes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice BES 2009 (Business Expansion Scheme)</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/11/15/loudervoice-bes-2009-business-expansion-scheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 15:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/11/15/loudervoice-bes-2009-business-expansion-scheme/</guid>
      <description>The LouderVoice customer reviews system for business has moved into high-gear in 2009. Clients are deploying our EasyReview widget on their e-commerce sites every week. Our first US customer will go live this month along with many more Irish sites. Our second UK site will go live early in the new year.
The most recent research by Internet Retailer tells you everything you need to know about how important reviews are to businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising Discussion on The Last Word</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/27/fundraising-discussion-on-the-last-word/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, I was on TodayFM&amp;rsquo;s The Last Word radio show with Professor Frank Roche talking to Matt Cooper. The topic was centered on fund raising in the current economic climate. You can hear what we had to say in this audio clip. The interview starts about 4 minutes 30 seconds in.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget that our 2008 BES offering is open until Dec 31st. The response to-date has been very positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon Solutions &amp; LouderVoice BES 2008</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 11:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/10/23/argolon-solutions-loudervoice-bes-2008/</guid>
      <description>We have just kicked off our BES 2008 offering which is built around the LouderVoice business. If you are interested in hearing more about this investment opportunity or discussing direct equity investments, please contact Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill on conor AT loudervoice DOT com or +353-87-9790297.
Over the past few months we have been trialling our business services with several clients. Some of those are already live, others will go live over the next quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A word of thanks</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 14:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/a-word-of-thanks/</guid>
      <description>Founders of start-ups tend to spend a lot of time griping about things. I could write an essay on how it took from Aug 28th to Dec 3rd for Enterprise Ireland to issue a document needed to get us BES approval. Instead I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the positive part of that story.
On Dec 3rd, EI shuffled the paperwork-exercise out the door and it arrived in the Revenue Commissioners. Our solicitors also submitted our RICT outline application around the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BES/SCS Briefing in Clarion on Monday</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-briefing-in-clarion-on-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 10:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-briefing-in-clarion-on-monday/</guid>
      <description>CorkBIC have arranged a briefing session on BES/SCS next Monday too. Whilst the Rubicon session is specifically targetted at start-ups, this one is more for the wider business community.
Short presentations will be made by:
Kevin Kenny, Tax Partner, Ernst &amp;amp; Young Clare Creamer, Assistant Principal, Revenue Commissioners Gerry O’Brien, Enterprise Ireland
Monday 12th November at 4pm – 5.15pm (to be followed by drinks reception) in the Clarion Hotel, Cork</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BES/SCS Session in Rubicon</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-session-in-rubicon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 10:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-session-in-rubicon/</guid>
      <description>A workshop on the 2007-2013 Business Expansion Scheme (BES) and Seed Capital Scheme (SCS) will take place on Monday 12th November at 13:00 p.m. in the Rubicon Centre.
The Revenue Commissioners (Cillian Byrne &amp;amp; Susan Cummins) will be presenting and Gerry O’Brien, Enterprise Ireland will also be in attendance. Focused on startup and developing companies, the format is a workshop as it is intended to be interactive and give you plenty of opportunity for questions and answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argolon BES Scheme</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/argolon-bes-scheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 19:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/argolon-bes-scheme/</guid>
      <description>We will be announcing our BES scheme as soon as the initial paperwork has been processed.
If you want to hear more about any of the investment opportunities in Argolon Solutions and the LouderVoice web-site please contact me via any of the methods listed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New BES limits OKed by EU!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/28/new-bes-limits-oked-by-eu/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just heard (via Joe Drumgoole&amp;rsquo;s blog) that the new BES limits annnounced last November have finally been approved by the EU. This is fantastic news.
This is the official EU newsletter announcement:
Notification or Registration Date:	23.05.2007 DG Responsible:	Competition DG Related Procedures:	N 311 / 2004
Decision on 23.08.2007:	Article 4§3 - decision not to raise objections
This presumably means that Enterprise Ireland should be processing new company certs starting five days ago and the Revenue Commissioners should be approving RICTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is EI refusing to do any pre-work for BES?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2007 10:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/19/why-is-ei-refusing-to-do-any-pre-work-for-bes/</guid>
      <description>As anyone who has kicked off a BES scheme knows there are a few simple steps you have to do in order to qualify. The key one is a &amp;ldquo;New Company Cert&amp;rdquo; from Enterprise Ireland or a CEB. To qualify for the cert they generally give you a small employment grant (a Feasibility Study Grant is not sufficient). You can then go to the Revenue and start the actual BES process itself and get in-principal approval for your scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from BarCampIreland SouthEast starting to appear</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</guid>
      <description>Keith has uploaded videos of the &amp;ldquo;Finding money for your start-up&amp;rdquo; session. I enjoyed the differing views of the panel on this topic but anyone who thought they&amp;rsquo;d come away with &amp;ldquo;so that&amp;rsquo;s how I do it&amp;rdquo; would have been disappointed. There should definitely be a follow-up session at BarCamp Dublin with a focus on successful early-stage tech startup fund-raising.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
