<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wceb on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/wceb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wceb on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 10:54:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/wceb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Idea Generation Workshop</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/06/09/idea-generation-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 10:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/06/09/idea-generation-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Very good idea from West Cork Enterprise Board:
They are running 3 one-day Idea Generation Workshops over the coming weeks. The workshops are for people who are thinking about starting their own business but don’t have a business idea in mind yet and also people who have a business idea but want to study the idea further.
They will help people decide whether self-employment is the right route for them. Topics covered during the workshop will include: What does it mean to be an entrepreneur?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Cork Enterprise Board Support</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/07/24/west-cork-enterprise-board-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 08:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/07/24/west-cork-enterprise-board-support/</guid>
      <description>I spent a very interesting afternoon talking to Christine O&amp;rsquo;Donovan in WCEB in Clonakilty on Tuesday. We covered a pretty wide range of topics and I was highly impressed by the range of services they offer local businesses.

Our big area of mutual frustration was the lack of take-up on the Tech-Check scheme. I&amp;rsquo;ve written about it before on my personal blog and in summary, if you are a local biz in Ireland with even one laptop and you&amp;rsquo;ve never even talked to an Enterprise Board, then you are missing out hugely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IIA Congress Discounts</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/28/iia-congress-discounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 08:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/28/iia-congress-discounts/</guid>
      <description>West Cork Enterprise Board contacted me last week to let me know about a discount offer they had received from the IIA for their client companies (and those of all CEBs). There was a further discount offered for being outside of Dublin too. Whilst the original price of €345 for non-members was just a bit at the high end for us, the double-discounted price of less than €150 is a bargain and I&amp;rsquo;ve signed up to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Small/Micro Businesses and the web</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/08/irish-smallmicro-businesses-and-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 15:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/08/irish-smallmicro-businesses-and-the-web/</guid>
      <description>A recurring conversation I have had recently is around very small non-technical Irish businesses having a web presence. I do a lot of Tech-Checks for the Cork CEBs and I continue to be surprised by how many of these businesses are invisible online.
One of the reasons for this may be that companies still think it costs a lot of money to have a web-site and non eircom.net email addresses. And there are still gougers out there charging people €2k for a simple off-the-shelf brochure site with stock graphics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
