<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>entrepreneur on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/entrepreneur/</link>
    <description>Recent content in entrepreneur on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 11:54:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/entrepreneur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Galway Open Coffee Announced!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/12/first-galway-open-coffee-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 11:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/12/first-galway-open-coffee-announced/</guid>
      <description>Aidan Finn just announced Galway OCC on Twitter. Upcoming.org page here. I&amp;rsquo;d been hoping for this one, I think it&amp;rsquo;ll be a big success. Looking forward to the reports. That plus BarCamp Galway are two great excuses for us to head up there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Coffee coverage on Read/WriteWeb</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/24/open-coffee-coverage-on-readwriteweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2007 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/24/open-coffee-coverage-on-readwriteweb/</guid>
      <description>David Lenehan has written a great overview of the Open Coffee phenomenon. Cork gets a mention. If you have any interest in building the start-up culture and community in Ireland then it is a must-read. If you like it, please Digg it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Much delayed post on Cork OCC visit to London</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/22/much-delayed-post-on-cork-occ-visit-to-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2007 09:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/22/much-delayed-post-on-cork-occ-visit-to-london/</guid>
      <description>This post should have been written over a week ago but I&amp;rsquo;m only finally getting the time now.
On Thursday 10th May, three of us from Cork Open Coffee (Walter Higgins, David Copithorne and myself) headed over to London Open Coffee. As someone who has never worked into the UK (The Netherlands and Germany being my main destinations in the past), I was pretty impressed to find myself standing outside the door of Waterstones on Regent Street at 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Coffee Comes to Waterford</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/26/open-coffee-comes-to-waterford/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2007 12:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/26/open-coffee-comes-to-waterford/</guid>
      <description>Congrats guys, I&amp;rsquo;ll be down for one soon, particularly as it&amp;rsquo;s free coffee if you visit from another OCC.
Waterford Open Coffee Club</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee - Robust discussion</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/13/cork-open-coffee-robust-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 14:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/13/cork-open-coffee-robust-discussion/</guid>
      <description>We had another good turnout this morning at Open Coffee and covered a lot of ground from technology companies not building good links with content companies to quite a long discussion about aims and metrics associated with Cork Open Coffee.
Haydn made some strong points about the fact that many web businesses are very heavily involved in content (the classic User Generated Content) but they seem to focus on business networking in a technology realm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Cork Open Coffee building the mix</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/01/second-cork-open-coffee-building-the-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 20:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/01/second-cork-open-coffee-building-the-mix/</guid>
      <description>We had the second Cork Open Coffee meet-up last Friday. As expected the numbers were down slightly but I was thrilled to see that over half the faces were new and we had some great additions to the attendee profile.
I had hoped when we kicked off OpenCoffee here that it would not just be about web people doing web stuff but would reach out to other technology business areas. So I was delighted to say hi to someone working in telecoms, to a developer from the Bay area (no not Bantry Bay) and to two people, new to the region, who work in multimedia and video production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second OpenCoffee this morning</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/30/second-opencoffee-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/30/second-opencoffee-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>Head on down to Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s any time between 10 and 12 and there should be some of us there talking tech and business and maybe a little Heroes. Particularly interested in talking to people about Coworking possibilities today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Coffee Club Ning Page</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/22/open-coffee-club-ning-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 09:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/22/open-coffee-club-ning-page/</guid>
      <description>Saul and the guys have setup a Ning page for Open Coffee. Ning is basically a social networking app. On the page you can see members, recent blog posts tagged with opencoffee, ditto pictures and more importantly Upcoming.org events that are tagged. It is one central place to find out what is happening in OpenCoffee globally.
On a more local level, as part of that, I have created an Upcoming.org group called (funnily enough) The Cork Open Coffee Club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee off to a flying start</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 17:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</guid>
      <description>Wow that was some morning in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s! I&amp;rsquo;d never been there before and the venue was just perfect. I arrived in to find a few of the guys along with Don the owner who stayed for the entire session. A huge thanks to Don for covering the cost of the refreshments today and for getting Wifi installed with almost no notice.
We had 20+ people turn up with the exact mix I was hoping for:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee Club Announcement</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 21:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of discussion the inaugural Cork OpenCoffee Club will be held at 10am this Friday 16th in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s on Emmet Place in Cork City Centre. UseAMap.
The aim of the club is to bring together a good mix of entrepreneurs, investors, developers and marketers, plus anyone else who is interested in growing the start-up community in Cork. Organisations like it@cork and the CorkBIC are incredibly important in fostering professional networking in Cork and I hope we can make OpenCoffee complementary in many ways to them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
