<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business-Intelligence on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/business-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business-Intelligence on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2005 23:46:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/business-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The power of so-called scripting languages</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/12/10/the-power-of-so-called-scripting-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2005 23:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/12/10/the-power-of-so-called-scripting-languages/</guid>
      <description>We have always been big fans of development languages which have traditionally been referred to as scripting languages.
Going back over 10 years, we created some very useful tools and automation systems using TCL. This may seem like an odd niche choice, but for us, at the time, it had some major advantages. It was cross-platform, it could easily interface to hardware systems like serial ports and it had a great third-party tool called FreeWrap which allowed one to create executables and not require our end-customers to install the full Tcl package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source nipping at Business Objects Heels?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2005/11/08/opensource-nipping-at-business-objects-heels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2005 09:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2005/11/08/opensource-nipping-at-business-objects-heels/</guid>
      <description>Business Objects have announced that they are joining the Eclipse Foundation and are going to Open Source some of their tools. This is a very timely move for them as there appears to be a lot of energy building behind their Open Source competitors which must surely be hurting sales of Crystal at the low-end.
Whilst none of the Open Source tools have the breadth and depth of Crystal&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, in many cases they are &amp;ldquo;good enough&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
