<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BAP on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/bap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BAP on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 22:59:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/bap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Interest in a Cork OpenCoffee Club meetup next week?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 22:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Starting with Saul in London followed quickly by Eoghan in Dublin and James/Jan in Limerick, it looks like the OpenCoffee Club idea really does have legs. The core idea is that a regular informal meeting is held in a coffee shop where we try to bring together entrepreneurs and investors to discuss topics of mutual interest, learn from each other and hopefully build lasting business relationships over time.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to propose an inaugural one in Cork City for next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must-read post over at the itnorthwest Blog</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 19:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/25/must-read-post-over-at-the-itnorthwest-blog/</guid>
      <description>Julian Ellison from Tablane has written the best summary of startup funding, finance and the Irish economy that I have ever read. I have one small contribution to make on it. He mentions the Business Angels Partnership and wonders how they &amp;ldquo;market&amp;rdquo; ideas that they receive.
I highly recommend that anyone with a strong well-thought out business plan just contact them and talk to them face to face. The basic way they work is that they help people who come in with strong ideas to ensure that the idea has legs and that some basic financial analysis and planning has been done.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
