<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technical on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/technical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technical on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 09:14:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/technical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using Android phone in Ireland</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/using-android-phone-in-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 09:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/using-android-phone-in-ireland/</guid>
      <description>I got an unlocked HTC G1 from the US recently for a project we are working on. This is the first Google Android phone and I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a full review soon. The first thing you have to do is activate the phone with Google and I immediately ran into problems. It turns out you need to add the Irish mobile network Access Points to the phone so it knows how to connect to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chrome on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/07/chrome-on-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 17:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/07/chrome-on-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>If you just can&amp;rsquo;t wait, Chrome will run on Ubuntu with a little help from Wine. Some scrappy fonts and I don&amp;rsquo;t think Flash works. But still, pretty darned impressive. Picasa 3 also seems to work well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Travel Tip</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/08/31/top-travel-tip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 16:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/08/31/top-travel-tip/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned before that a few months back I was in London for an event and I decided to forego my laptop and just bring my Nokia N95-8GB. This would provide e-mail, RSS reading and Twitter. Of course I was petrified of the roaming data charges that can happen abroad and made sure to just use Wifi where possible. Unfortunately my hotel room had a very poor wifi signal so I decided to bite the bullet and check my email using the (much maligned by me) Vodafone Live APN on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N810 leaves me cold</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/06/22/n810-leaves-me-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 10:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/06/22/n810-leaves-me-cold/</guid>
      <description>I really thought I would love this device considering how much I like its old N770 brother. However it completely misses the mark and I can find no place for it in my daily workflow. Dare I say it, I would prefer an iPod Touch!
Last May at Cork OpenCoffee, Gordon Murray told everyone about an amazing bargain on Expansys. Nokia N770 Internet Tablets were selling for approx €100. By the end of the coffee morning, more than 10 had been ordered and after a few hours humming and hawing I got one too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outcome of testing Mobile Broadband (O2 and Vodafone)</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/06/10/outcome-of-testing-mobile-broadband-o2-and-vodafone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 15:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/06/10/outcome-of-testing-mobile-broadband-o2-and-vodafone/</guid>
      <description>This is actually a combined review of O2 and Vodafone Ireland mobile broadband services since I tested them in parallel. Neither is a replacement for fixed-line BB but in certain situations, the O2 modem is extremely fast and was my winner overall.
I&amp;rsquo;ve railed against both O2 and Voda on repeated occasions for not offering decent value proper data plans on phones. I&amp;rsquo;ve also read a wide variety of opinions on the various mobile broadband offferings with Three getting the most abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Nokia N95-8GB</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/03/16/review-of-nokia-n95-8gb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 21:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/03/16/review-of-nokia-n95-8gb/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for the ultimate business phone rather than the gadget equivalent of a Prada handbag, then this is the device for you. Quite simply the best phone I&amp;rsquo;ve ever owned.
Cards on the table - I love this phone. I&amp;rsquo;d marry it if it was legal. The rest of this review is an ode to &amp;ldquo;what computers have become&amp;rdquo;.
I&amp;rsquo;ve generally owned middle-of-the-road good business phones, all Nokia, with two short lived diversions to Panasonic and Sony-Ericcson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaiku Invites</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/03/03/jaiku-invites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 10:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/03/03/jaiku-invites/</guid>
      <description>Jaiku Invites is a great initiative from Ciarán Rooney. When Google bought Jaiku they shut down new user registrations. There are a lot of people out there who would love to join and take part in all the great discussions we have there, particularly around events like OpenCoffee and BarCamps. Luckily each existing member was given 10 invites that they could hand out.
The purpose of Jaiku Invites is to hook these two groups of people together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movable Type - Not there yet</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/19/movable-type-not-there-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2008 12:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/19/movable-type-not-there-yet/</guid>
      <description>There has been some new buzz about Movable Type since version 4 was released a while back. I had carried out one install of v3 previously to ensure that we supported it ok in LouderVoice. It was one of the worst install experiences I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had. I&amp;rsquo;d prefer to build XEmacs from source on Windows. V3 made me realise why Wordpress had left MT eating its dust. The WP boast of a 5 minute install was not an empty one and it &amp;ldquo;just works&amp;rdquo; out of the box in most cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS Seminar in Cork</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/10/15/gps-seminar-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 08:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/10/15/gps-seminar-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>I was sent information about a very meaty looking three day seminar organised by GPS Ireland in the NMCI facility of CIT in Ringaskiddy. It&amp;rsquo;s on from 22nd-24th October.
Day 1 is aboout Fundamentals of GPS/GNSS and is open to anyone interested in seeking conceptual and detailed explanations of GPS technology, operation, capabilities, applications and development trends.
Day 2 is a follow-on from the first day and is about GPS Fundamentals &amp;amp; Enhancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderMinis now on Jaiku too</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 08:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</guid>
      <description>We announced LouderTweets recently, which are 140 character mini-reviews you can send to LouderVoice from Twitter without needing a LouderVoice account.
Last night we turned on LouderViesti which is the equivalent feature for the superb Jaiku. Jaiku is like Twitter but can do much much more. They are based in Finland and are adding great features at a fast rate.
We are now calling LouderTweets+LouderViesti = LouderMinis!
Using LouderViesti is even easier than LouderTweets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
