<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>polldaddy on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/polldaddy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in polldaddy on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 23:34:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/polldaddy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Mashable Open Web Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/13/the-mashable-open-web-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 23:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/13/the-mashable-open-web-awards/</guid>
      <description>If you like what we are doing over on LouderVoice, why not vote for us in the Mashable Open Web Awards. You can do it below.
 Mashable Open Web Awards
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to vote for all your favourite Irish WebApps, many of which can be found over at Web2Ireland.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chronicle the development of an app and a business?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/04/29/chronicle-the-development-of-an-app-and-a-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 20:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/04/29/chronicle-the-development-of-an-app-and-a-business/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Murray of eWrite was asking on Twitter this evening what people thought of the idea of him documenting publicly the development of his new product and the business around it. In other words, blogging about it, warts and all.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a superb idea and could be of great benefit both to his business and to others who read it. If he can build a good readership then it could become a focal point for people to discuss lots of the standard issues around building a technology business in Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galway OpenCoffee this Friday</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/01/galway-opencoffee-this-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/01/galway-opencoffee-this-friday/</guid>
      <description>Aidan Finn and David Lenehan (aka PollDaddy Lenny) are having an impromptu Galway OCC, Friday 11am Forster Court Hotel. All welcome. Spread the word</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote for PollDaddy in the Webware 100</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/11/vote-for-polldaddy-in-the-webware-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 14:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/11/vote-for-polldaddy-in-the-webware-100/</guid>
      <description>Not just because it is a brilliant product but also because Lenny, Jonathan and the guys have shown that small Irish technology companies can have global reach!
These guys pushed out 14 million polls last month and over half of them were non-English-language.
Vote early and often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice covered on Read/WriteWeb</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/30/loudervoice-covered-on-readwriteweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 08:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/30/loudervoice-covered-on-readwriteweb/</guid>
      <description>We were chuffed to bits and tickled pink this morning to see that David Lenehan has done an article about Irish webapps on the very highly regarded Read/WriteWeb site and we got a mention!
Thanks guys.
He also profiled some of the older guys like Pigsback and newer ones like Pixenate, Putplace and Nooked and not forgetting PollDaddy itself.
If you liked what David had to say, maybe consider voting for it over at Digg?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
