<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CorkBIC on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/corkbic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CorkBIC on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 10:34:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/corkbic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BES/SCS Briefing in Clarion on Monday</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-briefing-in-clarion-on-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 10:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/11/07/besscs-briefing-in-clarion-on-monday/</guid>
      <description>CorkBIC have arranged a briefing session on BES/SCS next Monday too. Whilst the Rubicon session is specifically targetted at start-ups, this one is more for the wider business community.
Short presentations will be made by:
Kevin Kenny, Tax Partner, Ernst &amp;amp; Young Clare Creamer, Assistant Principal, Revenue Commissioners Gerry O’Brien, Enterprise Ireland
Monday 12th November at 4pm – 5.15pm (to be followed by drinks reception) in the Clarion Hotel, Cork</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee Club Announcement</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 21:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/11/cork-opencoffee-club-announcement/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of discussion the inaugural Cork OpenCoffee Club will be held at 10am this Friday 16th in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s on Emmet Place in Cork City Centre. UseAMap.
The aim of the club is to bring together a good mix of entrepreneurs, investors, developers and marketers, plus anyone else who is interested in growing the start-up community in Cork. Organisations like it@cork and the CorkBIC are incredibly important in fostering professional networking in Cork and I hope we can make OpenCoffee complementary in many ways to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interest in a Cork OpenCoffee Club meetup next week?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 22:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/07/interest-in-a-cork-opencoffee-club-meetup-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Starting with Saul in London followed quickly by Eoghan in Dublin and James/Jan in Limerick, it looks like the OpenCoffee Club idea really does have legs. The core idea is that a regular informal meeting is held in a coffee shop where we try to bring together entrepreneurs and investors to discuss topics of mutual interest, learn from each other and hopefully build lasting business relationships over time.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to propose an inaugural one in Cork City for next week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
