<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 15:44:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork III Next Weekend</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/11/07/barcamp-cork-iii-next-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 15:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/11/07/barcamp-cork-iii-next-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As co-organiser of the first two Cork BarCamps, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to see the third one is happening next Saturday 14th Nov in the fabulous Cork International Airport Hotel. The able organisers this time around are Gordon Murray, Ciara Crossan and Ciara Feely.
BarCamp is one of those free conferences where you leave having gained far more from the day than you expect. It&amp;rsquo;s the serendipity that makes it special. I have built many friendships and business relationships with the people I meet there over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idea Generation Workshop</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/06/09/idea-generation-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 10:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/06/09/idea-generation-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Very good idea from West Cork Enterprise Board:
They are running 3 one-day Idea Generation Workshops over the coming weeks. The workshops are for people who are thinking about starting their own business but don’t have a business idea in mind yet and also people who have a business idea but want to study the idea further.
They will help people decide whether self-employment is the right route for them. Topics covered during the workshop will include: What does it mean to be an entrepreneur?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want to speak at next Facebook Garage Ireland?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/05/19/want-to-speak-at-next-facebook-garage-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 09:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/05/19/want-to-speak-at-next-facebook-garage-ireland/</guid>
      <description>The first Facebook Garage Ireland was a massive success with 150+ people in attendance and a bunch of great talks and demos.
We&amp;rsquo;re planning the next one for June and have put the call out for speakers/demoers.
If you are doing anything with FB Apps or Connect and want to let people know, then grab the opportunity. Remember, we had RTE at the last one and made the news!
All details over on the Web2Ireland blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Web Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/13/le-web-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 10:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/13/le-web-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I attended Le Web on Tue/Wed this week in Paris. It is the leading web conference in Europe and this was my third year.
Despite a bunch of logistical problems, Loic and Geraldine Le Meur created yet another event that will stick in the mind for a long time. I was at the conference with multiple hats on:
  CEO of LouderVoice eager to meet potential partners and investors Guest Author for ReadWriteWeb looking at Le Web from technology perspective Co-Editor of Web2Ireland looking at Le Web from business perspective   My Web2Ireland post covers the general business mood and how it may affect Irish start-ups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Blogger/Start-Up Dinner</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/06/cork-bloggerstart-up-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2008 16:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/06/cork-bloggerstart-up-dinner/</guid>
      <description>At Cork OpenCoffee yesterday we conned convinced Joe Scanlon to organise the Cork Blogger &amp;amp; Start-Up Dinner. It&amp;rsquo;s on December 15th at 5pm in Market Lane on Oliver Plunkett Street and you just have to leave a comment over on the blog to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogger and Startup Christmas Parties</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/21/blogger-and-startup-christmas-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 14:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/21/blogger-and-startup-christmas-parties/</guid>
      <description>Niall Harbison from iFoods is arranging a blogger and tech-start-up Christmas lunch/party in Dublin for December 17th. If you are interested in attending, leave a comment on the blog.
  photo credit: kyz
We were looking into doing similar in Cork but have realised that we are flat-out with travel and meetings in the run up to Christmas. So that leaves two options - someone else grab the baton and arrange it instead of us or have a post-Christmas party in the horrible dead time around mid January.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Annual Conference Announced</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/10/07/itcork-annual-conference-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 13:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/10/07/itcork-annual-conference-announced/</guid>
      <description>The it@cork annual conference has just been announced. Its title is &amp;ldquo;GREEN IT: Reduce CO2, Raise Profits&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s on November 26 in the lovely Radisson SAS Hotel in Cork.
The line-up looks like an excellent mix with the focus being clearly on Green as it relates to IT and Business. I particularly like the profit angle given the turmoil the world is going through right now
The is an Early Bird Discount available – Book on or before October 31 and it&amp;rsquo;s €250 for members, €350 for non members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork II on November 1st</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/30/barcamp-cork-ii-on-november-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 08:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/30/barcamp-cork-ii-on-november-1st/</guid>
      <description>It has been over two years since the last one, but BarCamp is finally coming back to Cork. It&amp;rsquo;s soon, very soon, only four weeks away. The venue is the lovely Webworks building in the City Centre, just like the last time.
We have a strong vision for this event and we need your help to make it happen on the day. Please read the first set of posts and give us your feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PodCamp is this Saturday</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/21/podcamp-is-this-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/21/podcamp-is-this-saturday/</guid>
      <description>PodCamp last year was one of my conference highlights and it looks like they are pulling out all the stops this year.
Head on down to Kilkenny this coming Saturday if you want to see what it&amp;rsquo;s all about. Tons of information and pre-conference activity on the PodCamp Ireland site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote in the it@cork Leaders Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/11/vote-in-the-itcork-leaders-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/11/vote-in-the-itcork-leaders-awards/</guid>
      <description>The second annual Leader&amp;rsquo;s Awards are on October 23rd in the Clarion Hotel, Lapps Quay, Cork. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice opportunity to recognise some of the leading companies and individuals in the region.
The winners last year were:
 Emerging Company Award - Cubic Telecom High Potential Award Abtran R&amp;amp;D Project Award - Treemetrics Academic Award - Cork Constraint Computation Centre (4Cs) IT Department Winner - Thomas Crosbie Holdings  Nominations close on September 23rd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
