<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ireland on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/ireland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ireland on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 13:31:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/ireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CIO For Ireland</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/10/10/cio-for-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 13:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/10/10/cio-for-ireland/</guid>
      <description>The new Programme for Government has been announced by the coalition in Ireland and one of the most important aspects of it is the announcement of the position of CIO. Whilst you might think this is only of interest to those who work in technology, I think it has the potential to be a critical role in preparing the country for renewal.
I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to seeing a CIO with real teeth and real vision who understands that information is power and power should be given to as many people as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Android phone in Ireland</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/using-android-phone-in-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 09:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/using-android-phone-in-ireland/</guid>
      <description>I got an unlocked HTC G1 from the US recently for a project we are working on. This is the first Google Android phone and I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a full review soon. The first thing you have to do is activate the phone with Google and I immediately ran into problems. It turns out you need to add the Irish mobile network Access Points to the phone so it knows how to connect to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our 2009 Predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 13:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/our-2009-predictions/</guid>
      <description>The 2008 predictions weren&amp;rsquo;t the most accurate. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how we do for 2009.
 The Android platform will be absolutely huge. With Motorola, Sony Ericsson and a raft of Tier 2 manufacturers signed up, it will become _the _mobile platform from the mid to high end. Ignore the HTC G1, that&amp;rsquo;s just a rough first attempt by one manufacturer.  Despite Android, iPhone will remain big. There is always that 10% of the market who like paying extra for &amp;ldquo;luxury&amp;rdquo; brands SaaS ecommerce providers will go mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A look back to last year&#39;s predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/a-look-back-to-last-years-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/a-look-back-to-last-years-predictions/</guid>
      <description>My predictions for 2008 were very hit and miss (mainly miss), here&amp;rsquo;s a quick re-cap:
  Cubic Telecom will have a £100m exit
 * Not yet. 2008 was an amazing year for Pat and the team with deals happening at breakneck pace.    European Founders, Howzat Media, TAG or Advent will do a deal with a web or mobile start-up here
 * Again not yet. I still think this will happen    More foreign VCs will invest in Irish web start-ups than Irish VCs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A possible web solution for small/micro biz</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/14/a-possible-web-solution-for-smallmicro-biz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/14/a-possible-web-solution-for-smallmicro-biz/</guid>
      <description>We had a great exchange of ideas on the previous post about ways of getting very small businesses online. Of particular interest to me are the companies with zero technical ability who just need a solution which involves them typing in some information about their company and then they have a web-presence.
One solution for this type of business is eWrite &amp;ldquo;Cork&amp;rdquo;. Up until now the eWrite guys, John and Gordon, have been focused more on the Small to Medium end of the market rather than the Micro to Small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Blogger Dinner</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/02/05/cork-blogger-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 19:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/02/05/cork-blogger-dinner/</guid>
      <description>Alexia Golez is arranging a Blogger Dinner in Cork for Sunday the 2nd March on the weekend of the Blogtalk Conference and WebCamp. You can expect some really interesting visitors (and locals!) to be there. Please let Alexia know if you wish to attend over on her blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you know of any free Wifi Hotspots?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/do-you-know-of-any-free-wifi-hotspots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 01:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/24/do-you-know-of-any-free-wifi-hotspots/</guid>
      <description>James Corbett is building a map of Wifi Hotspots around the country. Whilst they can be free or non-free, I hope we can identify as many free ones as possible first. I&amp;rsquo;ve added the ones I know of in Cork and indicated whether they are publicly accessible locations or not.

If you know of any, please spread the love and add a push-pin to the map. You should also include any FON hotspots that you know of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoiltchild looking for advice</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/10/29/spoiltchild-looking-for-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 22:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/10/29/spoiltchild-looking-for-advice/</guid>
      <description>Good post from Alan of Spoiltchild wondering about their investment strategy for Toddle and future apps. If you have any knowledge in this area, why not head over and leave a comment?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Leader Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/09/05/itcork-leader-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2007 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/09/05/itcork-leader-awards/</guid>
      <description>This is such a great idea.
On November 1, 2007 it@cork will have their first ever Leader’s Awards. They want to recognise some of the leading companies and individuals in the community and have an evening of networking, reflection and celebration.
There are 4 categories:
 1. Emerging Company Award - to recognise a leading company in early stage business planning and execution 2. High Potential Award - to recognise a leading established company driving forward in international markets 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have your start-up profiled by Ireland&#39;s number one ranked blogger</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 23:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</guid>
      <description>If you have a tech start-up and despair sometimes (as I do) over the lack of local press coverage of your efforts then help is at hand. Damien Mulley is offering to profile those who send him their company details. According to Technorati, he is the highest ranked blogger in Ireland and he also writes for the The Sunday Tribune so this can get you lots of interest.
Who knows, maybe certain startup-clueless newspapers (yes I&amp;rsquo;m talking about you Irish Examiner) might even pick up on it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
