<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startups on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/startups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startups on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 11:40:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/startups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yes, 1000 times, yes.</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/09/20/yes-1000-times-yes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 11:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/09/20/yes-1000-times-yes/</guid>
      <description>Read Pat Phelan&amp;rsquo;s post on &amp;ldquo;Irish Silicon Valley&amp;rdquo; now, right now.
I don&amp;rsquo;t need to add anything except, please listen to the man, he knows what he is talking about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQPrize Biz Plan Competition - Only 5 days to go!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/05/07/iqprize-biz-plan-competition-only-5-days-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 16:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/05/07/iqprize-biz-plan-competition-only-5-days-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Got a great business idea? Think you can put together a 5-page business plan in the next 5 days? The IQPrize is €10k for the best biz plan, with absolutely no strings attached.

The judges (including yours truly) are as follows:
 Aodhan Cullen, founder &amp;amp; CEO, StatCounter Colm Long, Head of Online Operations (EMEA), Facebook Conor O’Neill, co-founder &amp;amp; CEO, LouderVoice Eamonn Fallon, co-founder &amp;amp; CEO, Daft.ie Gail Power, Senior Manager, Google Martha Rotter, Internet Evangelist, Microsoft  And there may be one more joining that list shortly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paddy&#39;s Valley in the Press</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/30/paddys-valley-in-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 10:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/30/paddys-valley-in-the-press/</guid>
      <description>The Irish Times has covered the latest press release about our Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley trip. The support of Enterprise Ireland in not just important but it is really getting noticed by the press. Finfacts also give us a mention and I was interviewed by Cork 103FM and ENN. There are still plenty of places left but we will be setting a cut-off date soon so head on over to the site, read all about it, ask questions, make comments and then sign up if you like the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moffett Field here we come</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/12/moffett-field-here-we-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 11:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/12/moffett-field-here-we-come/</guid>
      <description>Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley has a definite date and now a hotel. And soon maybe even a t-shirt. We&amp;rsquo;ll set a closing date for signing up soon and spaces are limited so I encourage you to do so today!
If you know anyone in the Valley who you think would like to meet a bunch of Irish start-ups and techies, please contact them and let them know the details. If they bite, let us know too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get an Irish David Heinemeier Hansson</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/how-to-get-an-irish-david-heinemeier-hansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 13:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/how-to-get-an-irish-david-heinemeier-hansson/</guid>
      <description>We have a deep rooted problem in Ireland with getting young people to take part in the start-up culture. Every kid who leaves college with a degree in engineering/computing/business in the US wants to build something great. Every kid who leaves college in Ireland with a degree in engineering/computing/business wants a nice job in a bank or multi-national. This has to change.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been interviewing people for many years in all my different jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign-Up for Paddy&#39;s Valley!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/15/sign-up-for-paddys-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2007 23:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/15/sign-up-for-paddys-valley/</guid>
      <description>Apologies for the lack of information forthcoming about Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley, the blame lays firmly at my door. Few quick updates:
 1. The dates have been decided, December 2nd to December 9th 2. we now have [an official blog](http://paddysvalley.org/). Please subscribe to the RSS feed 3. [Damien has listed](http://www.mulley.net/2007/06/14/paddys-valley-what-exactly-do-we-want-to-do/) some of our ideas 4. Even if you signed up on the old wiki, please [re-sign up here](http://www.formspring.com/forms/paddysvalley-registration) 5. We&#39;re going to set a cut-off date for sign-ups very soon and we will probably be asking for a small deposit to cover basic expenses between now and the trip 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interviewed for Morning Ireland</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/17/interviewed-for-morning-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2007 20:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/17/interviewed-for-morning-ireland/</guid>
      <description>I did a short interview with Emma McNamara this afternoon for Radio 1. The overall theme of her piece was &amp;ldquo;The Economy&amp;rdquo; and as with other items in the series they took a regional focus which was Cork/Munster on this occasion.
I talked for far too long about the start-up scene down here, Open Coffee, LouderVoice, PaddysValley, the Ireland=Romania state of Venture Capital here and the difficulty many have in getting access to capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Graham nails it</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/28/paul-graham-nails-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2007 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/28/paul-graham-nails-it/</guid>
      <description>I read a LOT of material about startups, entrepreneurs, funding and technology but Paul Graham&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Why to Not Not Start a Startup&amp;rdquo; is one of the smartest things I&amp;rsquo;ve read in a long time.
I constantly wonder why we don&amp;rsquo;t see more startups in Ireland, particularly by young people who have little to lose. Here are all the reasons Paul gives why YOU aren&amp;rsquo;t doing it, and shows why most (but not all) should be ignored:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
