<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>microformats on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/microformats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in microformats on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 09:02:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/microformats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderTweets getting noticed</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/15/loudertweets-getting-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/15/loudertweets-getting-noticed/</guid>
      <description>When one of the most famous web design gurus on the planet, whose books we adore, says he likes something you&amp;rsquo;ve built, well it&amp;rsquo;s a damned nice feeling indeed.
So Dan Cederholm likes LouderTweets.

We&amp;rsquo;ve been getting LouderTweets from as far away as Japan and The Philippines. Keep them coming.
Just to give a sense of the variety of those mini-reviews, some of the most recent were:
 A movie: &amp;ldquo;Live Free or Die Hard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderMinis now on Jaiku too</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 08:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</guid>
      <description>We announced LouderTweets recently, which are 140 character mini-reviews you can send to LouderVoice from Twitter without needing a LouderVoice account.
Last night we turned on LouderViesti which is the equivalent feature for the superb Jaiku. Jaiku is like Twitter but can do much much more. They are based in Finland and are adding great features at a fast rate.
We are now calling LouderTweets+LouderViesti = LouderMinis!
Using LouderViesti is even easier than LouderTweets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Twitter Mash-Up</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 12:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</guid>
      <description>After a few late nights we&amp;rsquo;re now ready to let you send reviews from Twitter to LouderVoice. We&amp;rsquo;re calling them LouderTweets and they are 140 character mini-reviews you can send using Web, SMS or IM via Twitter to LouderVoice.
An important point is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a LouderVoice member to send LouderTweets but you should join if you want to rate, bookmark and build/share useful collections of reviews and mini-reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Launches</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 13:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday we quietly unveiled LouderVoice. If you want a reviews site which takes a fundamentally different approach to everyone else then you&amp;rsquo;ll like what we have built.
Bloggers who write reviews now have a site which is built around enabling them to publish reviews to blogs in a widely accepted format. Everyone else now has a site where they can find great reviews, read them on those blogs and then rate them, share them and subscribe to more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme change</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/theme-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 15:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/theme-change/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m testing out Scott Allan Wallick&amp;rsquo;s blog.txt theme. I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of Sandbox and this is very impressive too. Minimalist but attractive. It is also highly configurable and has lots of hAtom and hCard goodness built-in. I prefer it to the old one we had here. Thoughts anyone?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That was a rollercoaster 12 months</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/12/24/that-was-a-rollercoaster-12-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2006 08:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/12/24/that-was-a-rollercoaster-12-months/</guid>
      <description>In one short year we&amp;rsquo;ve gone from building web-based datacenter management and planning tools for our customer&amp;rsquo;s customers to starting our own web application development and getting ready to launch it. If you&amp;rsquo;d asked me a year ago where we&amp;rsquo;d be today, I would probably have said &amp;ldquo;doing the same thing as now&amp;rdquo;. I love being wrong.
The launch of the Structured Blogging initiative last December kicked off our interest in microformats both as end-users and from a business perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real World Live Clipboard</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/10/03/real-world-live-clipboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2006 19:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/10/03/real-world-live-clipboard/</guid>
      <description>Why are Microsoft and Eventful not shouting this from the rooftops?
You can now find an event in Eventful (e.g. this Divine Comedy one in Cork), right-click the Live Clipboard Icon, click copy, go to Windows Live Writer and do paste. Not only do you now have all that event information in your blog post, it is fully marked-up as a hCalendar item and you can link to the original source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Live Writer now supports microformats</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/10/03/windows-live-writer-now-supports-microformats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2006 19:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/10/03/windows-live-writer-now-supports-microformats/</guid>
      <description>It has been clear from the work being done by Ray Ozzie&amp;rsquo;s team on Live Clipboard that Microsoft were throwing their weight behind the microformats initiative but up until now it has just been in the technical demos of Live Clipboard.
This afternoon I was watching the interview Jon Udell did with Jack Ozzie and JJ Allaire on the new beta of Live Writer, an excellent new blog writing tool for Windows in which this post is being written.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XFN tweaks</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/09/15/xfn-tweaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2006 10:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/09/15/xfn-tweaks/</guid>
      <description>Phil Haack (greatest ever surname for a geek), has proposed some improvements to the XFN microformat including the most excellent fReNd-4-eVA.
He thinks he has serious issues with worrying about whether to mark someone as a friend or an acquaintance. What if you use &amp;ldquo;friend&amp;rdquo; but they use &amp;ldquo;acquaintance&amp;rdquo;? Rest assured that I have struggled with the same sad questions myself. I also worry that I&amp;rsquo;ll be considered a bit needy if I mark someone as a friend too soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>d.Construct 2006 - well worth the trip</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/09/11/dconstruct-2006-well-worth-the-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 08:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/09/11/dconstruct-2006-well-worth-the-trip/</guid>
      <description>d.Construct 2006 Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-09-08
Rating: 4 out of 5
Last Friday was dConstruct 2006 and I headed over not really knowing what to expect. The quality of speakers overall was excellent and I&amp;rsquo;m only disappointed that I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to meet more people - over 300 people in the room made it hard to pick names off name badges.
Jeff Barr of Amazon kicked the day off and was entertaining but I was aware of most of the content already.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
