<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>start-ups on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/start-ups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in start-ups on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 16:42:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/start-ups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quotes from Conor in today&#39;s Sunday Business Post</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/06/14/quotes-from-conor-in-todays-sunday-business-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/06/14/quotes-from-conor-in-todays-sunday-business-post/</guid>
      <description>The SBP has an excellent supplement about Cork in today&amp;rsquo;s edition. Hopefully it&amp;rsquo;ll make it onto their web-site at some stage. Caroline Allen dedicated the entire back page to start-ups and include quotes from CorkBIC, Rubicon Centre, it@cork and Argolon/LouderVoice. The full piece is well worth a read, particularly considering the same message was coming loud and clear from us all. Hopefully someone in Government will read it and get that message!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShareIT Presentation</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/25/shareit-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 20:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/25/shareit-presentation/</guid>
      <description>The first ShareIT session was held yesterday in UCC. Unfortunately I had to leave early but I did catch Jenny Kent&amp;rsquo;s and Krishna De&amp;rsquo;s presentations both of which were excellent and full of practical nuggets rather than generalities. This is a genuinely valuable initiative for those starting out in tech businesses. I highly recommend attending the next one in Dublin on April 28th in the Microsoft offices.
My presentation on &amp;ldquo;Oursourcing - A Guide&amp;rdquo; is here as a PDF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last call for attendees for free training session tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/23/last-call-for-attendees-for-free-training-session-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2007 16:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/23/last-call-for-attendees-for-free-training-session-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>The first ShareIT session is tomorrow. Remember, it is totally free and you&amp;rsquo;ll learn a bunch if you turn up. I&amp;rsquo;ve just finished writing my presentation on &amp;ldquo;Outsourcing - A Guide&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s a cracker :-)
More info on the Business Advisory site.
Contact Damien on 086 825 8586 if you want to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShareIT happening this Saturday</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/19/shareit-happening-this-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2007 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/19/shareit-happening-this-saturday/</guid>
      <description>I previously mentioned the ShareIT initiative by the Irish Small Business Advisory Group and the first session is on this coming Saturday in UCC. Put simply
The areas which will be covered in Cork include:
 Bootstrapping a small independent software vendor Effective communications How to use outsourcing to grow a small IT business Marketing research for Tech Startups Search Engine Optimisation for your website Managing web projects Sales in the IT environment  I&amp;rsquo;ll be giving the presentation on &amp;ldquo;How to use outsourcing to grow a small IT business&amp;rdquo; based on many years providing outsourcing services and now making heavy use of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from BarCampIreland SouthEast starting to appear</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/15/videos-from-barcampireland-southeast-starting-to-appear/</guid>
      <description>Keith has uploaded videos of the &amp;ldquo;Finding money for your start-up&amp;rdquo; session. I enjoyed the differing views of the panel on this topic but anyone who thought they&amp;rsquo;d come away with &amp;ldquo;so that&amp;rsquo;s how I do it&amp;rdquo; would have been disappointed. There should definitely be a follow-up session at BarCamp Dublin with a focus on successful early-stage tech startup fund-raising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BusinessAdvisory Training Sessions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/13/businessadvisory-training-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 12:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/13/businessadvisory-training-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Damien has just announced the Share IT Free Training sessions which he has organised under the umbrella of BusinessAdvisory.ie. This is a fantastic idea where those with expertise in certain areas give training for free to those who are seeking it.
Initially it the focus is on IT/Technology but if it proves successful, I&amp;rsquo;m sure the scope will expand. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to be able to do my bit and share what little knowledge I have in a few areas on the first training day in UCC on March 24th.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
