<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coworking on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/coworking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coworking on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 08:08:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/coworking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hot Desking and Incubation Centres in Cork</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/09/hot-desking-and-incubation-centres-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 08:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/09/hot-desking-and-incubation-centres-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a great meeting with Paul Healy of the Rubicon Incubation Centre in CIT in Cork. This has been a runaway success since it opened a year ago and I wanted to find out more. The Centre is probably best know for the Genesis Enterprise Programme but actually offers a lot more than this.
The Centre has not had a lot of marketing around it and I wondered why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee off to a flying start</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 17:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/16/cork-opencoffee-off-to-a-flying-start/</guid>
      <description>Wow that was some morning in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s! I&amp;rsquo;d never been there before and the venue was just perfect. I arrived in to find a few of the guys along with Don the owner who stayed for the entire session. A huge thanks to Don for covering the cost of the refreshments today and for getting Wifi installed with almost no notice.
We had 20+ people turn up with the exact mix I was hoping for:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coworking and Twitter come together in Twazr</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/coworking-and-twitter-come-together-in-twazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/coworking-and-twitter-come-together-in-twazr/</guid>
      <description>James over at Eirepreneur has very neatly brought together the idea of Coworking with Twitter. He has taken the Twitter feeds of a set of Irish developers and freelancers that he knows and spliced them into Grazr. It provides a single combined feed of a set of people who are all in Ireland, work in similar areas and know each other to some degree.
It gives that extra bit of socialisation that freelancers need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geek Dinners, BarCamps and Coworking</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/geek-dinners-barcamps-and-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/02/22/geek-dinners-barcamps-and-coworking/</guid>
      <description>I attended my first UK Geek Dinner last night after FoWA. Guests of honour were Tara Hunt and Chris Messina. I only chatted to Chris for a short while towards the end of the night and the bulk of the conversation was about BarCamp. I told him how important I thought BarCamps have been for the creation of a vibrant tech community in Ireland. I also wanted to thank him and Tantek and the others for starting something that I think is a true revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
