<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tom-Raftery on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/tom-raftery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tom-Raftery on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 17:19:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/tom-raftery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hasta Luego Blogger Dinner</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/06/05/hasta-luego-blogger-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 17:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/06/05/hasta-luego-blogger-dinner/</guid>
      <description>As many people know, Tom Raftery is moving to Spain in the near future. Tom is, of course, a famous blogger and tech consultant but that sells him short. His energy, enthusiasm and openness should be a model for us all. I know I&amp;rsquo;m going to miss him locally, and not just from it@cork and OpenCoffee. At least we&amp;rsquo;ll still have him online :-)
To give him the send-off he deserves, I thought it might be nice to have a bloggers&#39; dinner in Cork before he goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first starring role</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/22/our-first-starring-role/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2007 07:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/22/our-first-starring-role/</guid>
      <description>Tom Raftery has posted his first ever video podcast and I&amp;rsquo;m the interviewee. We spend quite a while talking about all the ins and outs of LouderVoice. I think Tom did a great job considering who he had to work with ;-)
Looking forward to seeing more Tom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rick Segal &amp; Shel Israel in Cork on Sept 9th</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/07/27/rick-segal-shel-israel-in-cork-on-sept-9th/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2006 12:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/07/27/rick-segal-shel-israel-in-cork-on-sept-9th/</guid>
      <description>Tom Raftery has posted that Rick Segal &amp;amp; Shel Israel are visiting Cork on Sept 9th as part of their world tour.
They are having a meet-up in Taste of Thailand and would love to talk to people with great ideas who can help them see how tech entrepreneurialism will evolve in Ireland over the next few years. They are also available to meet earlier in the day but will shoot anyone who appears with a powerpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it@cork Web2.0 Conference - Review Intro</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-review-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 09:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/10/itcork-web20-conference-review-intro/</guid>
      <description>it@cork Web2.0 Conference Event type: Conference
Date: 2006-06-08
Rating: 5 out of 5
Tom, Catherine and all the team at IT@Cork put on a fantastic half day Web 2.0 conference on Thursday.
The geek dinner the night before set the scene perfectly - thanks again to Damien and all the organisers of that and Stormhoek for the wine. I finally got to meet Damien, Donncha, Gavin and a few others who I had previously only known through their blogs like Branedy and his lovely wife.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
