<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>twitter on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/twitter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in twitter on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 11:16:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s not the property market, it&#39;s Twitter!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/05/its-not-the-property-market-its-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 11:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/05/its-not-the-property-market-its-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Brian Cowen got it all wrong in the December budget. Exchequer receipts were not down in 2007 due to the property market collapse, it&amp;rsquo;s because we were all on Twitter.
Pat Phelan and Florian Seroussi have calculated a $13.5B hit to the global economy due to Twitter usage reducing productivity in 2007. Using the Runge Kutta Algorithm adjusted by the gAb factor, that&amp;rsquo;s a €4B hit on the Irish economy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Twitter Mash-Up</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 12:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</guid>
      <description>After a few late nights we&amp;rsquo;re now ready to let you send reviews from Twitter to LouderVoice. We&amp;rsquo;re calling them LouderTweets and they are 140 character mini-reviews you can send using Web, SMS or IM via Twitter to LouderVoice.
An important point is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a LouderVoice member to send LouderTweets but you should join if you want to rate, bookmark and build/share useful collections of reviews and mini-reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coworking and Twitter come together in Twazr</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/coworking-and-twitter-come-together-in-twazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/03/06/coworking-and-twitter-come-together-in-twazr/</guid>
      <description>James over at Eirepreneur has very neatly brought together the idea of Coworking with Twitter. He has taken the Twitter feeds of a set of Irish developers and freelancers that he knows and spliced them into Grazr. It provides a single combined feed of a set of people who are all in Ireland, work in similar areas and know each other to some degree.
It gives that extra bit of socialisation that freelancers need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
