<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2008 on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/2008/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2008 on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:59:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/2008/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A look back to last year&#39;s predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/a-look-back-to-last-years-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/12/27/a-look-back-to-last-years-predictions/</guid>
      <description>My predictions for 2008 were very hit and miss (mainly miss), here&amp;rsquo;s a quick re-cap:
  Cubic Telecom will have a £100m exit
 * Not yet. 2008 was an amazing year for Pat and the team with deals happening at breakneck pace.    European Founders, Howzat Media, TAG or Advent will do a deal with a web or mobile start-up here
 * Again not yet. I still think this will happen    More foreign VCs will invest in Irish web start-ups than Irish VCs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Argolon/LouderVoice 2008 Predictions</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/01/01/the-argolonloudervoice-2008-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 12:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/01/01/the-argolonloudervoice-2008-predictions/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a few quick ones off the top of my head:
 Cubic Telecom will have a £100m exit European Founders, Howzat Media, TAG or Advent will do a deal with a web or mobile start-up here More foreign VCs will invest in Irish web start-ups than Irish VCs One of the current batch of Irish Web 2.0 start-ups will go global in a big way EI&amp;rsquo;s €170m VC fund will continue to provide minimal benefits to Irish web start-ups Eircom&amp;rsquo;s small fund will result in two major web start-up successes Someone will launch a full Y Combinator/Seedcamp here Minister John McGuinness will be given responsibility for re-structuring all state bodies concerned with business EI will absorb Údarás na Gaeltachta EI will launch a self-contained web unit with its own budget, minimal red-tape, firewall access to Facebook and based in the Cork Gaeltacht or Kilkenny Damien Mulley will launch his own start-up Six Apart will launch a free version of Typepad Six Apart or Automattic will launch a full blown social network built on their blogging platforms Facebook Sign-to-Noise will continue to plummet as more and more people join and repeat usage plateaus (How many FB apps did I have to install this week just to read happy new year messages?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
