<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startups on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/startups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startups on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2007 13:58:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/startups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Should Governments just get out of the way?</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/10/24/should-governments-just-get-out-of-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2007 13:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/10/24/should-governments-just-get-out-of-the-way/</guid>
      <description>Whilst I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of conversations with other start-ups about how the Government can help entrepreneurs more, I&amp;rsquo;ve also had a few with those who think it should do less.
One of those, an ex-pat Irish Angel, whose thoughts we hope to be able to share with a wider audience in the coming weeks, sent me this link to an article in The Economist.
The Fading Lustre of Clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Irish Start-Ups Through To SeedCamp</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/30/no-irish-start-ups-through-to-seedcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 19:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/30/no-irish-start-ups-through-to-seedcamp/</guid>
      <description>I was disappointed to see that no Irish start-ups made it through to the initial 20 on SeedCamp. My gut tells me this is simply due to lack of applications. I only knew of one start-up here that applied. Did you? As the old ad goes &amp;ldquo;if you&amp;rsquo;re not in, you can&amp;rsquo;t win&amp;rdquo;.
Maybe when they see the great outcome for the winners of the first one, we&amp;rsquo;ll have more youngfellas and youngwans getting up of their bums and giving it a go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeedCamp off to a flying start</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/08/15/seedcamp-off-to-a-flying-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2007 07:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/08/15/seedcamp-off-to-a-flying-start/</guid>
      <description>Saul Klein reports that they received over 260 applications from around Europe for SeedCamp. I hope there is a bunch of Irish ones in there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paddy&#39;s Valley in the Press</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/30/paddys-valley-in-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 10:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/30/paddys-valley-in-the-press/</guid>
      <description>The Irish Times has covered the latest press release about our Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley trip. The support of Enterprise Ireland in not just important but it is really getting noticed by the press. Finfacts also give us a mention and I was interviewed by Cork 103FM and ENN. There are still plenty of places left but we will be setting a cut-off date soon so head on over to the site, read all about it, ask questions, make comments and then sign up if you like the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have your start-up profiled by Ireland&#39;s number one ranked blogger</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 23:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/18/have-your-start-up-profiled-by-irelands-number-one-ranked-blogger/</guid>
      <description>If you have a tech start-up and despair sometimes (as I do) over the lack of local press coverage of your efforts then help is at hand. Damien Mulley is offering to profile those who send him their company details. According to Technorati, he is the highest ranked blogger in Ireland and he also writes for the The Sunday Tribune so this can get you lots of interest.
Who knows, maybe certain startup-clueless newspapers (yes I&amp;rsquo;m talking about you Irish Examiner) might even pick up on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get an Irish David Heinemeier Hansson</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/how-to-get-an-irish-david-heinemeier-hansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 13:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/how-to-get-an-irish-david-heinemeier-hansson/</guid>
      <description>We have a deep rooted problem in Ireland with getting young people to take part in the start-up culture. Every kid who leaves college with a degree in engineering/computing/business in the US wants to build something great. Every kid who leaves college in Ireland with a degree in engineering/computing/business wants a nice job in a bank or multi-national. This has to change.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been interviewing people for many years in all my different jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeedCamp Launches - apply now!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 12:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/03/seedcamp-launches-apply-now/</guid>
      <description>At the Essential Web conference last week Saul Klein announced SeedCamp. This is an incredibly important initiative that will help grow the spirit of entrepreneurship across Europe. It basically takes a YCombinator type model and implements it here.
For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, YCombinator is hugely successful project of Paul Graham in the US. Twice a year, once in Boston, once in SV, they ask (pre)startups to apply for a slot on the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spam-protected eWrite Forms</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/29/spam-protected-ewrite-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 14:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/29/spam-protected-ewrite-forms/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Murray from eWrite is a Cork OpenCoffee stalwart and his eWrite business has been very successful in Ireland. They provide web CMSes and Apps for SMEs. They have put a lot of work into protecting the forms on their customers sites against spam and recently decided to spin this out as a product in itself.
This is one of those simple but extremely useful apps. You can select from a set of forms on the eWrite Forms site and then embed that on your own site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign-Up for Paddy&#39;s Valley!</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/15/sign-up-for-paddys-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2007 23:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/15/sign-up-for-paddys-valley/</guid>
      <description>Apologies for the lack of information forthcoming about Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley, the blame lays firmly at my door. Few quick updates:
 1. The dates have been decided, December 2nd to December 9th 2. we now have [an official blog](http://paddysvalley.org/). Please subscribe to the RSS feed 3. [Damien has listed](http://www.mulley.net/2007/06/14/paddys-valley-what-exactly-do-we-want-to-do/) some of our ideas 4. Even if you signed up on the old wiki, please [re-sign up here](http://www.formspring.com/forms/paddysvalley-registration) 5. We&#39;re going to set a cut-off date for sign-ups very soon and we will probably be asking for a small deposit to cover basic expenses between now and the trip 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote for PollDaddy in the Webware 100</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/11/vote-for-polldaddy-in-the-webware-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 14:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/11/vote-for-polldaddy-in-the-webware-100/</guid>
      <description>Not just because it is a brilliant product but also because Lenny, Jonathan and the guys have shown that small Irish technology companies can have global reach!
These guys pushed out 14 million polls last month and over half of them were non-English-language.
Vote early and often.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
