<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LouderVoice on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/categories/loudervoice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LouderVoice on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 12:16:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/categories/loudervoice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice, Ireland’s Review &amp; Rate Solutions Company to Pay €35,000 to Web Partners</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2010/03/03/loudervoice-irelands-review-rate-solutions-company-to-pay-e35000-to-web-partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 12:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2010/03/03/loudervoice-irelands-review-rate-solutions-company-to-pay-e35000-to-web-partners/</guid>
      <description>Cross-posting this from the LouderVoice Blog:
We have just launched a new partner program paying out substantial commission and bonus payments to web professionals, developers and marketers that refer customers.
LouderVoice is Ireland’s largest and longest standing provider of Review &amp;amp; Rate (R&amp;amp;R) solutions to e-businesses. These solutions give customers the ability to post reviews of a products or services on the website they bought from. R&amp;amp;R tools are seen by market analysts as one of the most important tools for any website serious about online business*.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mashable Open Web Awards</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/11/13/the-mashable-open-web-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 23:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/11/13/the-mashable-open-web-awards/</guid>
      <description>If you like what we are doing over on LouderVoice, why not vote for us in the Mashable Open Web Awards. You can do it below.
 Mashable Open Web Awards
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to vote for all your favourite Irish WebApps, many of which can be found over at Web2Ireland.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderTweets getting noticed</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/15/loudertweets-getting-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/15/loudertweets-getting-noticed/</guid>
      <description>When one of the most famous web design gurus on the planet, whose books we adore, says he likes something you&amp;rsquo;ve built, well it&amp;rsquo;s a damned nice feeling indeed.
So Dan Cederholm likes LouderTweets.

We&amp;rsquo;ve been getting LouderTweets from as far away as Japan and The Philippines. Keep them coming.
Just to give a sense of the variety of those mini-reviews, some of the most recent were:
 A movie: &amp;ldquo;Live Free or Die Hard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at Essential Web 07</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/loudervoice-at-essential-web-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 09:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/loudervoice-at-essential-web-07/</guid>
      <description>We sent out this press release yesterday:
The purpose of the event is to provide a picture of the status and temperature of the web scene in Europe. The sessions will have a mix of upcoming and hot web companies - some will be pre-funded, raw start-ups, others will be well-funded and well-known.
&amp;ldquo;This as an incredible opportunity for us to attract further funding from world-class investors.&amp;rdquo; said CEO, Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderMinis now on Jaiku too</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 08:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/25/louderminis-now-on-jaiku-too/</guid>
      <description>We announced LouderTweets recently, which are 140 character mini-reviews you can send to LouderVoice from Twitter without needing a LouderVoice account.
Last night we turned on LouderViesti which is the equivalent feature for the superb Jaiku. Jaiku is like Twitter but can do much much more. They are based in Finland and are adding great features at a fast rate.
We are now calling LouderTweets+LouderViesti = LouderMinis!
Using LouderViesti is even easier than LouderTweets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Twitter Mash-Up</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 12:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</guid>
      <description>After a few late nights we&amp;rsquo;re now ready to let you send reviews from Twitter to LouderVoice. We&amp;rsquo;re calling them LouderTweets and they are 140 character mini-reviews you can send using Web, SMS or IM via Twitter to LouderVoice.
An important point is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a LouderVoice member to send LouderTweets but you should join if you want to rate, bookmark and build/share useful collections of reviews and mini-reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our first starring role</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/22/our-first-starring-role/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2007 07:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/22/our-first-starring-role/</guid>
      <description>Tom Raftery has posted his first ever video podcast and I&amp;rsquo;m the interviewee. We spend quite a while talking about all the ins and outs of LouderVoice. I think Tom did a great job considering who he had to work with ;-)
Looking forward to seeing more Tom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interviewed for Morning Ireland</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/17/interviewed-for-morning-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2007 20:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/17/interviewed-for-morning-ireland/</guid>
      <description>I did a short interview with Emma McNamara this afternoon for Radio 1. The overall theme of her piece was &amp;ldquo;The Economy&amp;rdquo; and as with other items in the series they took a regional focus which was Cork/Munster on this occasion.
I talked for far too long about the start-up scene down here, Open Coffee, LouderVoice, PaddysValley, the Ireland=Romania state of Venture Capital here and the difficulty many have in getting access to capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Launches</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 13:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday we quietly unveiled LouderVoice. If you want a reviews site which takes a fundamentally different approach to everyone else then you&amp;rsquo;ll like what we have built.
Bloggers who write reviews now have a site which is built around enabling them to publish reviews to blogs in a widely accepted format. Everyone else now has a site where they can find great reviews, read them on those blogs and then rate them, share them and subscribe to more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at TheNextWeb</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/04/19/loudervoice-at-thenextweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 23:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/04/19/loudervoice-at-thenextweb/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re attending TheNextWeb Conference in Amsterdam on June 1st. It looks like it will be an awesome day and we are aiming to show off LouderVoice to a big audience. The organisers have put together an awards site and we&amp;rsquo;d really appreciate a vote for LouderVoice in the Beta &amp;amp; Stealth Category. Whilst you are there, a vote for Pixenate in the Disruptors Category would make a lot of sense!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
