<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hReview on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/hreview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hReview on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 18:45:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/hreview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multiple LouderVoice Updates</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/06/24/multiple-loudervoice-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 18:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/06/24/multiple-loudervoice-updates/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy few weeks.
 Two years after LouderVoice launched with the aim to make reviews more useful via Microformats, Google announced support, followed quickly by several of our competitors. What took ye so long? Then we launched Ireland&amp;rsquo;s first Google Android Mobile application Then we enabled the use of simple #review to identify mini-reviews on Twitter Then Krishna De of Biz Growth Newsreleased an extended interview with CEO Conor all about ratings and reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderTweets getting noticed</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/07/15/loudertweets-getting-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/07/15/loudertweets-getting-noticed/</guid>
      <description>When one of the most famous web design gurus on the planet, whose books we adore, says he likes something you&amp;rsquo;ve built, well it&amp;rsquo;s a damned nice feeling indeed.
So Dan Cederholm likes LouderTweets.

We&amp;rsquo;ve been getting LouderTweets from as far away as Japan and The Philippines. Keep them coming.
Just to give a sense of the variety of those mini-reviews, some of the most recent were:
 A movie: &amp;ldquo;Live Free or Die Hard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Twitter Mash-Up</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 12:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/06/13/loudervoice-twitter-mash-up/</guid>
      <description>After a few late nights we&amp;rsquo;re now ready to let you send reviews from Twitter to LouderVoice. We&amp;rsquo;re calling them LouderTweets and they are 140 character mini-reviews you can send using Web, SMS or IM via Twitter to LouderVoice.
An important point is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a LouderVoice member to send LouderTweets but you should join if you want to rate, bookmark and build/share useful collections of reviews and mini-reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Launches</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 13:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2007/05/06/loudervoice-launches/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday we quietly unveiled LouderVoice. If you want a reviews site which takes a fundamentally different approach to everyone else then you&amp;rsquo;ll like what we have built.
Bloggers who write reviews now have a site which is built around enabling them to publish reviews to blogs in a widely accepted format. Everyone else now has a site where they can find great reviews, read them on those blogs and then rate them, share them and subscribe to more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technorati microformats search review</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2006/06/01/technorati-microformats-search-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 04:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2006/06/01/technorati-microformats-search-review/</guid>
      <description>Technorati microformats search Category: Search engine
Topic: microformats
Year created: 2006
Overall rating: 4 out of 5
Content rating: 3 out of 5
Design rating: 4 out of 5
Navigation rating: 4 out of 5
I was supposed to attend a microformats dinner tonight in SF but was stymied by the impossibility of parking a car anywhere in that city. I returned to my hotel to catch up on the latest blogs to find a post from Tantek from Technorati announcing the launch of their microformats search.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
