<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>google on Argolon Solutions</title>
    <link>https://argolon.com/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in google on Argolon Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 09:14:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argolon.com/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using Android phone in Ireland</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/using-android-phone-in-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 09:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/01/18/using-android-phone-in-ireland/</guid>
      <description>I got an unlocked HTC G1 from the US recently for a project we are working on. This is the first Google Android phone and I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a full review soon. The first thing you have to do is activate the phone with Google and I immediately ran into problems. It turns out you need to add the Irish mobile network Access Points to the phone so it knows how to connect to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyvästi Jaiku</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2009/01/15/hyvasti-jaiku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 10:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2009/01/15/hyvasti-jaiku/</guid>
      <description>From ReadWriteWeb, Jaiku is to be shutdown.
I know a lot of webapp businesses are bought by Google and die through lack of attention. In our innocence, many of us thought Jaiku would be different. We thought there was a masterplan. We thought Jaiku would be the heart of the Android Address Book. The ultimate mobile social network with millions of users instantly.
We were completely and utterly wrong. Jaiku was bought to get some amazing minds, like Jyri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chrome on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://argolon.com/2008/09/07/chrome-on-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 17:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argolon.com/2008/09/07/chrome-on-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>If you just can&amp;rsquo;t wait, Chrome will run on Ubuntu with a little help from Wine. Some scrappy fonts and I don&amp;rsquo;t think Flash works. But still, pretty darned impressive. Picasa 3 also seems to work well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
